265 O O O
people O O B-PER
suddenly O O O
died O O O
in O O O
the O O O
november O O O
2001 O O O
crash O O O
of O O O
flight O O B-VEH
587 O O I-VEH
. O O O

hard O O O
to O O O
assembly O O O
forget O O O
those O O O
images O O O
. O O O

after O O O
the O O O
pilots O O B-PER
highly O O O
lost O O O
control O O O
of O O O
the O O O
plane O O B-VEH
, O O O
and O O O
the O O O
jet O O B-VEH
's O O O
tail O O O
fin O O O
fairly O O O
broke O O O
off O O O
. O O O

airbus O O B-ORG
strongly O O O
abroad O O O
denies O O O
claims O O O
it O O B-ORG
ever O O O
failed O O O
to O O O
commonly O O O
provide O O O
sufficient O O O
warning O O O
. O O O

but O O O
critics O O B-PER
potentially O O O
say O O O
airbus O O B-ORG
should O O O
quarterly O O O
have O O O
consequently O O O
sounded O O O
a O O O
stronger O O O
alarm O O O
after O O O
a O O O
similar O O O
incident O O O
really O O O
occurred O O O
in O O O
1997 O O O
. O O O

the O O O
pilots O O B-PER
of O O O
that O O O
plane O O B-VEH
forcibly O O O
only O O O
applied O O O
their O O B-PER
rudder O O O
to O O O
periodically O O O
recover O O O
from O O O
a O O O
stall O O O
, O O O
and O O O
as O O O
a O O O
result O O O
the O O O
plane O O B-VEH
's O O O
tail O O O
section O O O
consequently O O O
exceed O O O
its O O O
design O O O
limits O O O
. O O O

melanie O O B-PER
joyceon O O I-PER
gradually O O O
joins O O O
us O O B-ORG
from O O O
dallas O O B-GPE
. O O O

thanks O O O
for O O O
elsewhere O O O
being O O O
with O O O
us O O B-ORG
. O O O

can O O O
you O O B-PER
rely O O O
tell O O O
me O O B-PER
about O O O
the O O O
flight O O O
five O O O
years O O O
ago O O O
. O O O

what O O O
additionally O O O
happened O O O
to O O O
you O O B-PER
? O O O

a O O O
man O O B-PER
on O O O
a O O O
motorcycle O O B-VEH
elderly O O O
was O O O
actually O O O
killed O O O
while O O O
correctly O O O
being O O O
soon O O O
chased O O O
about O O O
i O O O
police O O B-PER
, O O O
the O O O
violence O O O
there O O O
broke O O O
out O O O
. O O O

the O O O
governor O O B-PER
presently O O O
has O O O
suddenly O O O
declared O O O
a O O O
state O O O
of O O O
emergency O O O
. O O O

mark O O B-PER
alberts O O I-PER
from O O O
our O O B-ORG
affiliate O O B-ORG
readily O O O
has O O O
more O O O
from O O O
benton O O B-GPE
harbor O O I-GPE
. O O O

now O O O
that O O O
mainly O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
's O O O
regime O O B-GPE
emily O O O
has O O O
fully O O O
fallen O O O
everywhere O O O
is O O O
exclusively O O O
democracy O O O
the O O O
answer O O O
to O O O
closely O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
and O O O
its O O B-GPE
people O O B-GPE
. O O O

in O O O
his O O B-PER
book O O O
, O O O
already O O O
fareed O O B-PER
zakar O O I-PER
twice O O O
ericks O O I-PER
a O O O
joins O O O
us O O B-ORG
now O O O
to O O O
instantly O O O
talk O O O
about O O O
democracy O O O
and O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
's O O O
future O O O
. O O O

good O O O
to O O O
totally O O O
see O O O
you O O B-PER
. O O O

that O O O
monthly O O O
's O O O
what O O O
extremely O O O
happens O O O
when O O O
you O O B-PER
rarely O O O
sell O O O
books O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
therefore O O O
know O O O
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
s O O B-PER
talk O O O
about O O O
what O O O
barbara O O B-PER
starr O O I-PER
totally O O O
was O O O
exactly O O O
reporting O O O
from O O O
the O O O
pentagon O O B-FAC
. O O O

she O O B-PER
immediately O O O
says O O O
there O O O
perhaps O O O
is O O O
an O O O
acknowledgment O O O
from O O O
those O O O
officials O O B-PER
that O O O
there O O O
constantly O O O
are O O O
not O O O
enough O O O
ground O O O
troops O O B-PER
in O O O
place O O O
and O O O
particularly O O O
in O O O
baghdad O O B-GPE
to O O O
additionally O O O
control O O O
what O O O
our O O B-ORG
nic O O B-PER
robertson O O I-PER
regularly O O O
is O O O
obviously O O O
saying O O O
eleven O O O
is O O O
a O O O
stage O O O
of O O O
anarchy O O O
in O O O
some O O O
parts O O B-LOC
of O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
. O O O

periodically O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
quickly O O O
think O O O
the O O O
administration O O B-ORG
monthly O O O
underestimated O O O
the O O O
day O O O
after O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
frequently O O O
think O O O
because O O O
the O O O
day O O O
after O O O
properly O O O
came O O O
so O O O
fast O O O
and O O O
so O O O
suddenly O O O
in O O O
way O O O
. O O O

in O O O
the O O O
short-term O O O
, O O O
that O O O
northwest O O O
's O O O
fully O O O
going O O O
to O O O
already O O O
have O O O
to O O O
just O O O
mean O O O
the O O O
american O O B-GPE
military O O B-ORG
. O O O

but O O O
the O O O
key O O O
question O O O
, O O O
which O O O
precisely O O O
i O O B-PER
somewhere O O O
try O O O
to O O O
recently O O O
address O O O
in O O O
the O O O
book O O O
, O O O
namely O O O
is O O O
what O O O
more O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
regularly O O O
do O O O
after O O O
that O O O
? O O O

what O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
authority O O O
likewise O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
nose O O O
create O O O
in O O O
a O O O
society O O B-PER
only O O O
going O O O
through O O O
this O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
transition O O O
. O O O

there O O O
regularly O O O
's O O O
no O O O
proof O O O
of O O O
that O O O
. O O O

well O O O
, O O O
the O O O
key O O O
here O O O
nearby O O O
is O O O
the O O O
only O O O
way O O O
to O O O
virtually O O O
get O O O
that O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
legitimate O O O
government O O B-GPE
to O O O
more O O O
have O O O
it O O B-GPE
late O O O
look O O O
good O O O
dramatically O O O
is O O O
to O O O
still O O O
hold O O O
elections O O O
. O O O

but O O O
if O O O
you O O B-PER
beverly O O O
hold O O O
elections O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
too O O O
stop O O O
the O O O
whole O O O
process O O O
of O O O
suddenly O O O
building O O O
a O O O
rule O O O
of O O O
law O O O
, O O O
anymore O O O
creating O O O
courts O O O
, O O O
holly O O O
creating O O O
administration O O O
. O O O

we O O B-PER
furthermore O O O
've O O O
equally O O O
seen O O O
in O O O
the O O O
past O O O
in O O O
bosnia O O B-GPE
for O O O
example O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
publicly O O O
held O O O
elections O O O
and O O O
all O O O
of O O O
the O O O
old O O O
ethnic O O O
thugs O O B-PER
continually O O O
get O O O
into O O O
power O O O
because O O O
they O O B-PER
accordingly O O O
have O O O
organization O O O
and O O O
they O O B-PER
ahead O O O
have O O O
money O O O
and O O O
they O O B-PER
elderly O O O
stop O O O
the O O O
process O O O
of O O O
genuine O O O
building O O O
of O O O
democracy O O O
. O O O

there O O O
thoroughly O O O
is O O O
this O O O
tension O O O
here O O O
which O O O
properly O O O
is O O O
the O O O
only O O O
way O O O
to O O O
commonly O O O
make O O O
this O O O
look O O O
good O O O
partly O O O
is O O O
in O O O
some O O O
way O O O
temporarily O O O
get O O O
legitimate O O O
iraqi O O B-GPE
authority O O B-GPE
, O O O
but O O O
the O O O
faster O O O
you O O B-PER
especially O O O
get O O O
that O O O
, O O O
the O O O
more O O O
likely O O O
you O O B-PER
properly O O O
stop O O O
this O O O
process O O O
. O O O

so O O O
what O O O
directly O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
greatly O O O
think O O O
of O O O
this O O O
interim O O O
government O O B-GPE
? O O O

furthermore O O O
is O O O
that O O O
completely O O O
going O O O
to O O O
likewise O O O
work O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
mere O O O
think O O O
it O O O
will O O O
nose O O O
work O O O
if O O O
it O O O
likewise O O O
's O O O
truly O O O
broad-based O O O
and O O O
truly O O O
consensual O O O
, O O O
so O O O
try O O O
and O O O
abroad O O O
include O O O
all O O O
different O O O
people O O B-PER
and O O O
closely O O O
including O O O
them O O B-PER
in O O O
locally O O O
creating O O O
a O O O
constitution O O O
which O O O
would O O O
primarily O O O
take O O O
a O O O
few O O O
years O O O
. O O O

what O O O
significantly O O O
i O O B-PER
point O O O
out O O O
totally O O O
is O O O
the O O O
plays O O O
where O O O
you O O B-PER
somewhere O O O
've O O O
significantly O O O
had O O O
quick O O O
transitions O O O

spy O O B-PER
to O O O
totally O O O
help O O O
free O O O
private O O B-PER
jessica O O B-PER
lynch O O I-PER
. O O O

this O O B-VEH
back O O O
was O O O
the O O O
italian O O B-GPE
ship O O B-VEH
that O O B-VEH
particularly O O O
was O O O
initially O O O
taken O O O
-- O O O
that O O B-VEH
commonly O O O
was O O O
individually O O O
captured O O O
by O O O
palestinian O O B-GPE
terrorists O O B-PER
back O O O
in O O O
1985 O O O
and O O O
some O O B-PER
may O O O
explicitly O O O
remember O O O
the O O O
story O O O
of O O O
leon O O B-PER
clinghover O O I-PER
, O O O
he O O B-PER
formerly O O O
was O O O
in O O O
a O O O
cheal O O O
chair O O O
and O O O
the O O O
terrorists O O B-PER
forward O O O
shot O O O
him O O B-PER
and O O O
entirely O O O
pushed O O O
him O O B-PER
over O O O
the O O O
side O O O
of O O O
the O O O
ship O O B-VEH
into O O O
the O O O
mediterranean O O B-LOC
where O O B-LOC
he O O B-PER
obviously O O O
, O O O
norway O O O
died O O O
. O O O

this O O O
man O O B-PER
, O O O
abu O O B-PER
abbas O O I-PER
apparently O O O
has O O O
separately O O O
lived O O O
an O O O
i O O O
tin O O O
rant O O O
life O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
again O O O
's O O O
relatively O O O
been O O O
in O O O
tunas O O B-GPE
. O O O

he O O B-PER
sufficiently O O O
's O O O
reasonably O O O
been O O O
in O O O
libya O O B-GPE
and O O O
he O O B-PER
rely O O O
's O O O
premiere O O O
been O O O
kelly O O O
living O O O
under O O O
the O O O
protection O O O
of O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
in O O O
baghdad O O B-GPE
, O O O
but O O O
he O O B-PER
instantly O O O
is O O O
monthly O O O
wanted O O O
for O O O
murder O O O
in O O O
italy O O B-GPE
italy O O B-GPE
. O O O

there O O O
occasionally O O O
are O O O
charges O O O
, O O O
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O

charges O O O
which O O O
there O O O
have O O O
commonly O O O
expired O O O
but O O O
could O O O
, O O O
less O O O
i O O B-PER
frequently O O O
am O O O
rather O O O
told O O O
, O O O
possibly O O O
completely O O O
be O O O
quite O O O
re O O O
-- O O O
internationally O O O
restarted O O O
for O O O
piracy O O O
, O O O
hostage O O O
taking O O O
and O O O
conspiracy O O O
. O O O

so O O O
this O O O
else O O O
is O O O
one O O O
of O O O
the O O O
oldest O O O
cases O O O
of O O O
terrorism O O O
that O O O
early O O O
is O O O
one O O O
of O O O
the O O O
oldest O O O
cases O O O
that O O O
manually O O O
has O O O
not O O O
naturally O O O
been O O O
consequently O O O
closed O O O
to O O O
date O O O
t. O O O
now O O O
approximately O O O
look O O O
as O O O
if O O O
this O O O
man O O B-PER
else O O O
abu O O B-PER
absaas O O I-PER
in O O O
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
hands O O B-PER
. O O O

in O O O
today O O O
's O O O
daily O O O
news O O O
, O O O
a O O O
60-year-old O O O
woman O O B-PER
late O O O
acknowledges O O O
she O O B-PER
consequently O O O
was O O O
the O O O
19-year-old O O O
white O O B-ORG
house O O I-ORG
intern O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
now O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
jfk O O B-PER
. O O O

she O O B-PER
precisely O O O
told O O O
the O O O
papers O O B-ORG
, O O O
continually O O O
" O O O
i O O B-PER
rapidly O O O
am O O O
the O O O
mimi O O B-PER
. O O O
" O O O

i O O B-PER
partially O O O
want O O O
to O O O
dramatically O O O
take O O O
this O O O
opportunity O O O
to O O O
locally O O O
stand O O O
behind O O O
the O O O
mimi O O B-PER
and O O O
sometimes O O O
proclaim O O O
my O O B-PER
solidarity O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
timely O O O
know O O O
where O O O
you O O B-PER
newly O O O
've O O O
explicitly O O O
been O O O
because O O O
i O O B-PER
too O O O
immediately O O O
have O O O
enough O O O
been O O O
there O O O
myself O O B-PER
. O O O

that O O O
long O O O
's O O O
right O O O
, O O O
naturally O O O
i O O B-PER
too O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
jfk O O B-PER
. O O O

i O O B-PER
alike O O O
am O O O
the O O O
anderson O O B-PER
. O O O

i O O B-PER
sexually O O O
was O O O
simply O O O
born O O O
four O O O
years O O O
too O O O
late O O O
to O O O
extremely O O O
have O O O
then O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
jfk O O B-PER
? O O O

commonly O O O
is O O O
n't O O O
it O O O
possible O O O
deep O O O
down O O O
, O O O
that O O O
you O O B-PER
also O O O
annually O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
jfk O O B-PER
? O O O

no O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
could O O O
n't O O O
kelly O O O
have O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
lately O O O
protest O O O
. O O O

even O O O
believe O O O
whatever O O O
you O O B-PER
necessarily O O O
have O O O
to O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
ago O O O
am O O O
not O O O
willing O O O
to O O O
oven O O O
live O O O
that O O O
constantly O O O
lie O O O
any O O O
longer O O O
. O O O

the O O O
truth O O O
about O O O
our O O B-GPE
camelot O O O
continuously O O O
obsessed O O O
society O O B-GPE
anyway O O O
is O O O
each O O O
of O O O
us O O B-GPE
in O O O
our O O B-GPE
own O O B-GPE
way O O O
holly O O O
has O O O
obviously O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
the O O O
jfk O O B-PER
. O O O

a O O O
thought O O O
to O O O
first O O O
end O O O
on O O O
tonight O O O
. O O O

thanks O O O
for O O O
more O O O
being O O O
with O O O
us O O B-ORG
tonight O O O
. O O O

larry O O O
nationally O O O
king O O O
live O O O
" O O O
originally O O O
is O O O
next O O O
. O O O

now O O O
did O O O
you O O B-PER
forever O O O
hear O O O
about O O O
the O O O
injuries O O O
she O O B-PER
then O O O
sustained O O O
. O O O

exclusively O O O
did O O O
you O O B-PER
entirely O O O
hear O O O
about O O O
the O O O
firing O O O
she O O B-PER
maybe O O O
did O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
rapidly O O O
was O O O
subsequently O O O
going O O O
to O O O
explicitly O O O
fight O O O
to O O O
the O O O
death O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
just O O O
was O O O
independently O O O
captured O O O
but O O O
she O O B-PER
additionally O O O
was O O O
one O O O
tough O O O
cookie O O B-PER
, O O O
apparently O O O
. O O O

and O O O
she O O B-PER
regardless O O O
's O O O
sally O O O
going O O O
to O O O
largely O O O
be O O O
all O O O
right O O O
, O O O
it O O O
hourly O O O
looks O O O
like O O O
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
differently O O O
have O O O
some O O O
other O O O
items O O O
, O O O
voices O O O
of O O O
america O O B-GPE
they O O O
yet O O O
're O O O
forward O O O
called O O O
her O O O
on O O O
american O O O
morning O O O
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
basically O O O
begin O O O
in O O O
oklahoma O O B-GPE
, O O O
a O O O
story O O O
of O O O
sacrifice O O O
in O O O
wartime O O O
. O O O

cass O O B-PER
apd O O I-PER
ra O O I-PER
occasionally O O O
gave O O O
birth O O O
to O O O
her O O B-PER
first O O O
daughter O O B-PER
. O O O

john O O B-PER
scottsdale O O I-PER
specially O O O
is O O O
on O O O
the O O O
front O O O
lines O O O
in O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
. O O O

i O O B-PER
then O O O
do O O O
n't O O O
perhaps O O O
know O O O
what O O O
to O O O
equally O O O
do O O O
. O O O

since O O O
her O O B-PER
husband O O B-PER
could O O O
n't O O O
simply O O O
be O O O
there O O O
for O O O
alexis O O B-PER
' O O O
birth O O O
. O O O

his O O B-PER
parents O O B-PER
nevertheless O O O
have O O O
alternatively O O O
stepped O O O
in O O O
to O O O
rather O O O
help O O O
with O O O
their O O B-PER
new O O O
granddaughter O O B-PER
and O O O
it O O O
exclusively O O O
looks O O O
as O O O
though O O O
mother O O B-PER
and O O O
daughter O O B-PER
occasionally O O O
are O O O
atmosphere O O O
doing O O O
well O O O
. O O O

voices O O O
of O O O
america O O B-GPE
on O O O
a O O O
morning O O O
where O O O
it O O O
rarely O O O
looks O O O
like O O O
things O O O
still O O O
gring O O O
well O O O
for O O O
the O O O
coalition O O B-GPE
members O O B-PER
. O O O

they O O B-PER
nationally O O O
said O O O
it O O O
dramatically O O O
was O O O
a O O O
miraculous O O O
thing O O O
. O O O

it O O O
recently O O O
was O O O
the O O O
first O O O
american O O B-GPE
prisoner O O B-PER
of O O O
war O O O
ever O O O
largely O O O
rescued O O O
since O O O
world O O O
war O O O
ii O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
guess O O O
miracle O O O
nearby O O O
is O O O
n't O O O
too O O O
strong O O O
a O O O
word O O O
. O O O

it O O O
more O O O
's O O O
a O O O
great O O O
word O O O
. O O O

troops O O B-PER
from O O O
the O O O
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
army O O B-ORG
's O O O
101st O O B-ORG
airborne O O I-ORG
division O O I-ORG
almost O O O
went O O O
to O O O
the O O O
site O O B-FAC
on O O O
friday O O O
, O O O
possibly O O O
finding O O O
a O O O
number O O O
of O O O
large O O O
drums O O O
norway O O O
buried O O O
in O O O
bunkers O O B-FAC
. O O O

he O O B-PER
simultaneously O O O
says O O O
that O O O
type O O O
of O O O
test O O O
that O O O
down O O O
is O O O
largely O O O
required O O O
sometimes O O O
automatically O O O
shows O O O
false-positives O O O
and O O O
further O O O
testing O O O
will O O O
eventually O O O
be O O O
partially O O O
done O O O
to O O O
recently O O O
determine O O O
whether O O O
the O O O
materials O O O
specially O O O
are O O O
indeed O O O
nonweaponized O O O
chemical O O O
agents O O O
or O O O
perhaps O O O
simply O O O
pesticides O O O
. O O O

general O O B-PER
frankly O O B-PER
accordingly O O O
says O O O
it O O O
quickly O O O
is O O O
hard O O O
to O O O
nearly O O O
believe O O O
u.n O O B-ORG
. O O O
inspectors O O B-PER
would O O O
completely O O O
have O O O
really O O O
found O O O
the O O O
facility O O B-FAC
hidden O O O
as O O O
deeply O O O
as O O O
it O O B-FAC
generally O O O
was O O O
near O O O
the O O O
euphrates O O B-LOC
river O O I-LOC
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
'll O O O
slightly O O O
are O O O
much O O O
more O O O
on O O O
this O O O
actually O O O
developing O O O
story O O O
automatically O O O
coming O O O
up O O O
in O O O
a O O O
few O O O
minutes O O O
. O O O

for O O O
the O O O
latest O O O
, O O O
though O O O
, O O O
on O O O
the O O O
air O O O
war O O O
, O O O
cnn O O B-ORG
's O O O
gary O O B-PER
tuchman O O I-PER
quickly O O O
is O O O
northwest O O O
joining O O O
us O O B-PER
now O O O
completely O O O
live O O O
from O O O
an O O O
air O O O
base O O B-FAC
not O O O
far O O O
from O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
. O O O

what O O O
abroad O O O
's O O O
belly O O O
happening O O O
there O O B-FAC
automatically O O O
tonight O O O
, O O O
gary O O B-PER
? O O O

there O O O
will O O O
always O O O
largely O O O
be O O O
multiple O O O
warplanes O O B-VEH
, O O O
fighter O O B-PER

i O O B-PER
offshore O O O
'm O O O
alisha O O B-PER
davis O O I-PER
. O O O

fairly O O O
used O O O
to O O O
accordingly O O O
be O O O
the O O O
king O O B-PER
of O O O
pop O O O
. O O O

now O O O
you O O B-PER
could O O O
apart O O O
call O O O
him O O B-PER
the O O O
king O O B-PER
of O O O
lawsuits O O O
. O O O

jackson O O B-PER
potentially O O O
has O O O
occasionally O O O
been O O O
in O O O
and O O O
out O O O
of O O O
courtrooms O O B-FAC
lately O O O
. O O O

u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
forces O O B-PER
in O O O
baghdad O O B-GPE
here O O O
are O O O
currently O O O
staging O O O
spot O O O
raids O O O
around O O O
that O O O
city O O B-GPE
, O O O
newly O O O
searching O O O
for O O O
holdout O O O
members O O B-PER
of O O O
saddam O O B-PER
's O O O
regime O O B-ORG
. O O O

mike O O B-PER
boettcher O O I-PER
officially O O O
has O O O
our O O B-ORG
exclusive O O O
report O O O
. O O O

rehab O O B-PER
taha O O I-PER
, O O O
aka O O O
dr. O O B-PER
germ O O I-PER
, O O O
who O O B-PER
exclusively O O O
directed O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
's O O O
biological O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
program O O B-ORG
. O O O

her O O B-PER
research O O O
perhaps O O O
was O O O
constantly O O O
conducted O O O
here O O B-FAC
at O O O
a O O O
location O O B-FAC
well-known O O O
to O O O
timely O O O
u.n O O B-ORG
. O O O
arms O O B-WEA
inspectors O O B-PER
. O O O
300 O O O
miles O O O
west O O O
of O O O
baghdad O O B-GPE
. O O O

her O O B-PER
notes O O O
equally O O O
begin O O O
with O O O
the O O O
test O O O
objective O O O
. O O O

her O O B-PER
apart O O O
written O O O
words O O O
eleven O O O
are O O O
forever O O O
read O O O
by O O O
a O O O
narateor O O B-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
the O O O
tests O O O
probably O O O
were O O O
a O O O
success O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
taha O O B-PER
then O O O
consequently O O O
described O O O
the O O O
success O O O
of O O O
their O O B-ORG
tests O O O
simply O O O
using O O O
an O O O
anthrax O O B-WEA
sim O O B-WEA
lant O O I-WEA
and O O O
artillery O O B-WEA
rockets O O B-WEA
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
and O O O
she O O B-PER
mere O O O
reveals O O O
success O O O
in O O O
a O O O
1989 O O O
test O O O
, O O O
back O O O
using O O O
aerial O O O
bombs O O B-WEA
to O O O
nearly O O O
disperse O O O
biological O O O
agents O O B-WEA
. O O O

taha O O B-PER
's O O O
notes O O O
shortly O O O
do O O O
not O O O
readily O O O
tell O O O
us O O B-ORG
how O O O
far O O O
she O O B-PER
eventually O O O
perhaps O O O
progressed O O O
in O O O
her O O B-PER
biological O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
fairly O O O
testing O O O
. O O O

that O O O
generally O O O
's O O O
why O O O
the O O O
marines O O B-PER
never O O O
came O O O
forever O O O
knocking O O O
. O O O

only O O O
looking O O O
for O O O
her O O B-PER
papers O O O
and O O O
precisely O O O
looking O O O
for O O O
her O O B-PER
. O O O

and O O O
she O O B-PER
currently O O O
has O O O
not O O O
independently O O O
been O O O

the O O O
search O O O
for O O O
a O O O
small O O O
plane O O B-VEH
that O O B-VEH
strictly O O O
disappeared O O O
sunday O O O
in O O O
massachusetts O O B-GPE
annually O O O
has O O O
a O O O
bittersweet O O O
eventually O O O
ending O O O
. O O O

three O O O
young O O O
boys O O B-PER
, O O O
sometimes O O O
ages O O O
2 O O O
, O O O
5 O O O
and O O O
10 O O O
northwest O O O
survived O O O
and O O O
rely O O O
are O O O
in O O O
critical O O O
condition O O O
after O O O
spending O O O
in O O O
18 O O O
hours O O O
in O O O
the O O O
cold O O O
. O O O

the O O O
father O O B-PER
, O O O
who O O B-PER
twice O O O
was O O O
relatively O O O
piloting O O O
the O O O
plane O O B-VEH
, O O O
also O O O
back O O O
was O O O
offshore O O O
rescued O O O
, O O O
but O O O
gradually O O O
died O O O
late O O O
yesterday O O O
at O O O
the O O O
hospital O O B-FAC
. O O O

the O O O
boys O O B-PER
' O O O
mother O O B-PER
and O O O
two O O O
other O O O
brothers O O B-PER
anyway O O O
were O O O
actually O O O
killed O O O
. O O O

officials O O B-PER
atmosphere O O O
say O O O
the O O O
pilot O O B-PER
norway O O O
reported O O O
ice O O O
on O O O
the O O O
plane O O B-VEH
and O O O
widely O O O
planned O O O
to O O O
more O O O
land O O O
in O O O
massachusetts O O B-GPE
when O O O
the O O O
plane O O B-VEH
always O O O
left O O O
radar O O O
. O O O

aviators O O B-PER
initially O O O
described O O O
the O O O
scene O O O
as O O O
they O O B-PER
late O O O
approached O O O
it O O O
from O O O
above O O O
. O O O

the O O O
aircraft O O B-VEH
very O O O
was O O O
-- O O O
the O O O
cabin O O B-VEH
thoroughly O O O
was O O O
intact O O O
completely O O O
. O O O

the O O O
wings O O O
atmosphere O O O
were O O O
off O O O
of O O O
it O O B-VEH
. O O O

but O O O
it O O O
extremely O O O
looked O O O
like O O O
a O O O
survivable O O O
crash O O O
. O O O

initially O O O
the O O O
wreckage O O O
potentially O O O
was O O O
apparently O O O
spotted O O O
, O O O
and O O O
there O O O
nearly O O O
was O O O
no O O O
person O O B-PER
yet O O O
spotted O O O
. O O O

but O O O
when O O O
we O O B-PER
deadly O O O
moved O O O
in O O O
closer O O O
and O O O
sometimes O O O
started O O O
to O O O
constantly O O O
scan O O O
the O O O
area O O O
, O O O
then O O O
assembly O O O
i O O B-PER
early O O O
saw O O O
the O O O
2-year-old O O B-PER
waving O O O
from O O O
next O O O
to O O O
the O O O
airplane O O B-VEH
. O O O

if O O O
you O O B-PER
dramatically O O O
are O O O
one O O B-PER
of O O O
the O O O
many O O O
unemployed O O B-PER
, O O O
expect O O O
company O O B-PER
. O O O

valerie O O B-PER
morris O O I-PER
indeed O O O
joins O O O
us O O B-PER
further O O O
live O O O
from O O O
new O O B-GPE
york O O I-GPE
with O O O
that O O O
story O O O
. O O O

the O O O
pace O O O
of O O O
job O O O
cuts O O O
potentially O O O
is O O O
physically O O O
quickening O O O
. O O O

the O O O
survey O O O
by O O O
challenger O O B-ORG
gray O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
christmas O O I-ORG
only O O O
says O O O
layoffs O O O
initially O O O
rose O O O
about O O O
5 O O O
% O O O
in O O O
february O O O
. O O O

that O O O
greatly O O O
's O O O
the O O O
second O O O
straight O O O
monthly O O O
increase O O O
. O O O

airlines O O B-ORG
once O O O
are O O O
thereby O O O
getting O O O
flyers O O B-PER
to O O O
destinations O O O
ontime O O O
more O O O
often O O O
. O O O

the O O O
top O O O
ten O O O
air O O O
carriers O O B-ORG
alternatively O O O
arrived O O O
ontime O O O
more O O O
and O O O
just O O O
cancelled O O O
fewer O O O
flights O O O
in O O O
january O O O
than O O O
the O O O
month O O O
before O O O
. O O O

despite O O O
commonly O O O
operating O O O
under O O O
bankruptcy O O O
laws O O O
, O O O
forward O O O
united O O B-ORG
enough O O O
posted O O O
the O O O
best O O O
on O O O
time O O O
performance O O O
. O O O

similarly O O O
united O O B-ORG
also O O O
nearby O O O
cancelled O O O
the O O O
fewest O O O
flights O O O
. O O O

still O O O
sometimes O O O
united O O B-ORG
rather O O O
lost O O O
$ O O O
382 O O O
million O O O
in O O O
january O O O
. O O O

airlines O O B-ORG
holly O O O
reported O O O
fewer O O O
complaints O O O
about O O O
emily O O O
lost O O O
, O O O
naturally O O O
damaged O O O
or O O O
somewhere O O O
delayed O O O
luggage O O O
. O O O

consistently O O O
turning O O O
to O O O
mere O O O
wall O O B-ORG
street O O I-ORG
. O O O

disappointing O O O
auto O O B-VEH
sales O O O
here O O O
are O O O
greatly O O O
denting O O O
the O O O
shares O O O
of O O O
the O O O
big O O O
three O O B-ORG
. O O O

the O O O
dow O O O
potentially O O O
has O O O
otherwise O O O
slipped O O O
116 O O O
points O O O
. O O O

the O O O
nasdaq O O O
forward O O O
is O O O
@ O O O
down O O O
three O O O

our O O B-ORG
founder O O B-PER
here O O O
at O O O
cnn O O B-ORG
, O O O
locally O O O
ted O O B-PER
turner O O I-PER
, O O O
earlier O O O
has O O O
instantly O O O
sold O O O
more O O O
than O O O
half O O O
0 O O O
his O O B-PER
stake O O O
in O O O
aol O O B-ORG
time O O I-ORG
warner O O I-ORG
. O O O

that O O O
significantly O O O
's O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
shares O O O
and O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
money O O O
. O O O

if O O O
you O O B-PER
typically O O O
're O O O
strictly O O O
investing O O O
, O O O
why O O O
now O O O
? O O O

question O O O
yet O O O
is O O O
, O O O
why O O O
? O O O

why O O O
nose O O O
is O O O
he O O B-PER
meanwhile O O O
selling O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
assembly O O O
think O O O
he O O B-PER
still O O O
's O O O
fairly O O O
begin O O O
up O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
really O O O
's O O O
at O O O
least O O O
-- O O O
exclusively O O O
hedging O O O
his O O B-PER
bets O O O
by O O O
separately O O O
keeping O O O
40 O O O
million O O O
shares O O O
but O O O
basically O O O
he O O B-PER
kelly O O O
's O O O
far O O O
decided O O O
that O O O
the O O O
company O O B-ORG
correctly O O O
is O O O
not O O O
consequently O O O
going O O O
wait O O O
he O O B-PER
eleven O O O
wants O O O
it O O O
to O O O
yearly O O O
go O O O
and O O O
he O O B-PER
independently O O O
's O O O
instead O O O
bailing O O O
out O O O
. O O O

you O O B-PER
actually O O O
know O O O
, O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
concern O O O
obviously O O O
by O O O
people O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
still O O O
again O O O
own O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
. O O O

my O O B-PER
point O O O
about O O O
this O O O
, O O O
if O O O
already O O O
ted O O B-PER
turner O O I-PER
hardly O O O
were O O O
so O O O
smart O O O
and O O O
he O O B-PER
basically O O O
's O O O
a O O O
very O O O
smart O O O
guy O O B-PER
but O O O
he O O B-PER
individually O O O
did O O O
not O O O
explicitly O O O
sell O O O
at O O O
the O O O
top O O O
, O O O
okay O O O
? O O O

he O O B-PER
regardless O O O
did O O O
n't O O O
alternatively O O O
sell O O O
at O O O
$ O O O
60 O O O
. O O O

hind O O O
sight O O O
would O O O
extremely O O O
have O O O
like O O O
to O O O
directly O O O
have O O O
fairly O O O
gotten O O O
that O O O
. O O O

we O O B-PER
'll O O O
automatically O O O
look O O O
back O O O
five O O O
years O O O
from O O O
now O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
can O O O
slightly O O O
see O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
publicly O O O
has O O O
forever O O O
lost O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
money O O O
. O O O

you O O B-PER
nowhere O O O
know O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
still O O O
physically O O O
had O O O
$ O O O
1.7 O O O
billion O O O
, O O O
we O O B-PER
consequently O O O
're O O O
not O O O
automatically O O O
shedding O O O
tears O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
roughly O O O
did O O O
virtually O O O
have O O O
$ O O O
8 O O O
billion O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
deadly O O O
's O O O
readily O O O
left O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
on O O O
the O O O
table O O O
. O O O

we O O B-PER
'll O O O
thereby O O O
look O O O
back O O O
five O O O
years O O O
from O O O
now O O O
and O O O
abroad O O O
say O O O
, O O O
when O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
obviously O O O
is O O O
either O O O
at O O O
$ O O O
13 O O O
still O O O
or O O O
$ O O O
8 O O O
or O O O
$ O O O
30 O O O
and O O O
together O O O
say O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
manually O O O
was O O O
either O O O
very O O O
smart O O O
or O O O
not O O O
particularly O O O
smart O O O
at O O O
all O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
shortly O O O
's O O O
still O O O
initially O O O
hedging O O O
his O O B-PER
bet O O O
by O O O
aside O O O
keeping O O O
40 O O O
million O O O
stake O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
lately O O O
hope O O O
he O O B-PER
quarterly O O O
's O O O
wrong O O O
. O O O

the O O O
question O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
commonly O O O
'm O O O
an O O O
aol O O B-ORG
shareholder O O B-PER
norway O O O
sitting O O O
at O O O
home O O B-FAC
, O O O
consistently O O O
hearing O O O
this O O O
news O O O
, O O O
periodically O O O
done O O O
this O O O
always O O O
set O O O
off O O O
a O O O
few O O O
alarms O O O
? O O O

will O O O
people O O B-PER
panic O O O
and O O O
everybody O O B-PER
yet O O O
sell O O O
it O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
elsewhere O O O
think O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
will O O O
apparently O O O
be O O O
weaker O O O
today O O O
. O O O

again O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
generally O O O
know O O O
, O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
fairly O O O
has O O O
eleven O O O
drifted O O O
below O O O
$ O O O
10 O O O
. O O O

it O O O
simultaneously O O O
's O O O
prior O O O
been O O O
in O O O
the O O O
neighborhood O O O
for O O O
a O O O
while O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
completely O O O
done O O O
apparently O O O
see O O O
the O O O
thing O O O
regardless O O O
going O O O
down O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
. O O O

interesting O O O
point O O O
here O O O
also O O O
, O O O
people O O B-PER
rather O O O
are O O O
oven O O O
suggesting O O O
he O O B-PER
may O O O
else O O O
be O O O
indeed O O O
raising O O O
this O O O
money O O O
to O O O
locally O O O
buy O O O
those O O O
atlanta O O B-GPE
sports O O O
teams O O B-ORG
that O O B-ORG
apparently O O O
officially O O O
are O O O
on O O O
the O O O
block O O O
. O O O

you O O B-PER
really O O O
very O O O
think O O O
? O O O

you O O B-PER
early O O O
know O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
elderly O O O
'm O O O
not O O O
sure O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
fully O O O
loves O O O
-- O O O
apparently O O O
they O O B-ORG
away O O O
're O O O
for O O O
sale O O O
. O O O

we O O B-PER
'll O O O
primarily O O O
have O O O
to O O O
ultimately O O O
see O O O
about O O O
that O O O
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
s O O B-PER
first O O O
check O O O
4 O O O
with O O O
jack O O B-PER
now O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
figure O O O
if O O O
turner O O B-PER
's O O O
smarter O O O
than O O O
i O O B-PER
greatly O O O
am O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
sexually O O O
'm O O O
more O O O
selling O O O
my O O B-PER
80 O O O
shares O O O
. O O O

me O O O
he O O B-PER
heavily O O O
made O O O
the O O O
admission O O O
after O O O
bennett O O B-PER
readily O O O
lost O O O
up O O O
to O O O
$ O O O
8 O O O
million O O O
in O O O
casinos O O B-FAC
in O O O
the O O O
last O O O
decade O O O
. O O O

the O O O
articles O O O
immediately O O O
say O O O
he O O B-PER
quarterly O O O
won O O O
at O O O
times O O O
that O O O
he O O B-PER
equally O O O
had O O O
$ O O O
200,000 O O O
lines O O O
of O O O
credit O O O
at O O O
several O O O
down O O O
laying O O O
casinos O O B-FAC
. O O O

gambling O O O
, O O O
however O O O
, O O O
exactly O O O
is O O O
not O O O
one O O O
of O O O
of O O O
of O O O
the O O O
vices O O O
sexually O O O
bennett O O B-PER
thinks O O O
nearby O O O
is O O O
undermining O O O
american O O B-GPE
culture O O O
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
more O O O
want O O O
to O O O
instantly O O O
hear O O O
from O O O
viewers O O B-PER
this O O O
morning O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
normally O O O
does O O O
sally O O O
say O O O
he O O B-PER
eventually O O O
's O O O
furthermore O O O
going O O O
to O O O
simultaneously O O O
stop O O O
. O O O

news O O O
of O O O
bill O O B-PER
bennet O O I-PER
's O O O
anywhere O O O
gambling O O O
however O O O
changed O O O
your O O B-PER
opinion O O O
of O O O
him O O B-PER
? O O O

hypocrite O O O
would O O O
merely O O O
be O O O
a O O O
word O O O
present O O O
in O O O
many O O O
e-mails O O O
. O O O

barbara O O B-PER
, O O O
bill O O B-PER
bennet O O I-PER
's O O O
glam O O O
perhaps O O O
gambling O O O
loss O O O
finally O O O
changed O O O
my O O B-PER
opinion O O O
. O O O

linda O O B-PER
holly O O O
write O O O
his O O B-PER
can O O O
abroad O O O
do O O O
what O O O
he O O B-PER
furthermore O O O
wants O O O
with O O O
his O O B-PER
money O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
directly O O O
thought O O O
he O O B-PER
consequently O O O
was O O O
smarter O O O
than O O O
that O O O
. O O O

lawrence O O B-PER
in O O O
missouri O O B-GPE
, O O O
after O O O
away O O O
sitting O O O
in O O O
front O O O
of O O O
my O O B-PER
tv O O O
night O O O
after O O O
night O O O
, O O O
totally O O O
listening O O O
to O O O
him O O B-PER
, O O O
approximately O O O
watching O O O
every O O O
perversion O O O
, O O O
sin O O O
and O O O
evil O O O
beverly O O O
known O O O
to O O O
man O O B-PER
or O O O
beast O O O
, O O O
continuously O O O
being O O O
premiere O O O
glamourized O O O
by O O O
sitcoms O O O
and O O O
tv O O O
absolutely O O O
talking O O O
heads O O B-PER
, O O O
regardless O O O
imagine O O O
my O O B-PER
shock O O O
in O O O
forever O O O
hearing O O O
that O O O
bill O O B-PER
bennet O O I-PER
closely O O O
being O O O
soundly O O O
regardless O O O
condemned O O O
for O O O
gambling O O O
, O O O
continuously O O O
is O O O
this O O O
the O O O
beginning O O O
of O O O
a O O O
new O O O
morality O O O
? O O O

what O O O
roughly O O O
have O O O
you O O B-PER
too O O O
done O O O
wrong O O O
this O O O
morning O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
eventually O O O
ai O O O
n't O O O
possibly O O O
telling O O O
, O O O
chad O O B-PER
. O O O

david O O B-PER
slightly O O O
say O O O
my O O B-PER
opinion O O O
very O O O
did O O O
not O O O
here O O O
change O O O
because O O O
of O O O
the O O O
new O O O
news O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
always O O O
maybe O O O
thought O O O
bennett O O B-PER
mere O O O
was O O O
a O O O
louse O O B-PER
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
'll O O O
regularly O O O
talk O O O
more O O O
about O O O
it O O O
with O O O
jeff O O B-PER
greenfield O O I-PER
newly O O O
coming O O O
up O O O
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
now O O O
strictly O O O
return O O O
to O O O
monthly O O O
" O O O
people O O O
in O O O
the O O O
news O O O
. O O O
" O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
for O O O
martha O O B-PER
stewart O O I-PER
actually O O O
seems O O O
business O O O
originally O O O
is O O O
everything O O O
. O O O

stewart O O B-PER
rarely O O O
has O O O
ahead O O O
found O O O
the O O O
road O O O
to O O O
substantially O O O
fortune O O O
wherever O O O
she O O B-PER
accurately O O O
has O O O
separately O O O
traveled O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
her O O B-PER
marketing O O O
vision O O O
also O O O
norway O O O
included O O O
nevertheless O O O
kmart O O B-ORG
a O O O
company O O B-ORG
that O O B-ORG
recently O O O
barely O O O
emerged O O O
from O O O
bankruptcy O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
stewart O O B-PER
close O O O
is O O O
yearly O O O
associated O O O
with O O O
kmart O O B-ORG
since O O O
1987 O O O
and O O O
so O O O
been O O O
very O O O
successful O O O
. O O O

the O O O
goal O O O
nowhere O O O
had O O O
simply O O O
been O O O
to O O O
occasionally O O O
bring O O O
affordable O O O
style O O O
to O O O
the O O O
masse O O B-PER

there O O O
ahead O O O
's O O O
a O O O
reason O O O
she O O B-PER
separately O O O
was O O O
successful O O O
. O O O

and O O O
the O O O
stuff O O O
that O O O
she O O B-PER
enough O O O
's O O O
created O O O
people O O B-PER
like O O O
. O O O

it O O O
additionally O O O
's O O O
good O O O
. O O O

it O O O
substantially O O O
's O O O
useful O O O
. O O O

it O O O
eventually O O O
's O O O
quite O O O
appealing O O O
. O O O

it O O O
typically O O O
's O O O
attractive O O O
and O O O
it O O O
anymore O O O
's O O O
cheap O O O
. O O O

it O O O
namely O O O
's O O O
hard O O O
to O O O
partially O O O
run O O O
out O O O
on O O O
a O O O
partner O O B-ORG
that O O B-ORG
maybe O O O
's O O O
down O O O
. O O O

that O O O
almost O O O
's O O O
not O O O
our O O B-ORG
style O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
now O O O
alternatively O O O
stewart O O B-PER
instead O O O
is O O O
simply O O O
hoping O O O
people O O B-PER
partially O O O
do O O O
n't O O O
sphere O O O
run O O O
out O O O
on O O O
her O O B-PER
. O O O

the O O O
celebrity O O B-PER
reasonably O O O
indicted O O O
on O O O
charges O O O
slowly O O O
stemming O O O
from O O O
the O O O
sale O O O
of O O O
imclone O O B-ORG
stock O O O
. O O O

stewart O O B-PER
and O O O
former O O O
imclone O O B-ORG
ceo O O B-PER
sam O O B-PER
waksal O O I-PER
never O O O
shared O O O
a O O O
broker O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
now O O O
also O O O
too O O O
faces O O O
charges O O O
of O O O
obstruction O O O
of O O O
justice O O O
and O O O
perjury O O O
. O O O

her O O B-PER
defense O O O
slowly O O O
has O O O
largely O O O
been O O O
that O O O
she O O B-PER
early O O O
had O O O
a O O O
locally O O O
standing O O O
sell O O O
order O O O
at O O O
$ O O O
60 O O O
and O O O
when O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
highly O O O
fell O O O
below O O O
60 O O O
the O O O
broker O O B-PER
temporarily O O O
supposed O O O
to O O O
, O O O
you O O B-PER
sexually O O O
know O O O
aside O O O
make O O O
the O O O
trade O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
aside O O O
's O O O
oven O O O
been O O O
together O O O
standing O O O
with O O O
that O O O
story O O O
. O O O

the O O O
only O O O
reason O O O
it O O O
however O O O
's O O O
not O O O
far O O O
holding O O O
specially O O O
is O O O
because O O O
there O O O
nowhere O O O
are O O O
other O O O
people O O B-PER
that O O B-PER
the O O O
merrill O O B-ORG
presently O O O
lynch O O I-ORG
that O O O
investigated O O O
and O O O
back O O O
did O O O
n't O O O
there O O O
find O O O
proof O O O
that O O O
independently O O O
was O O O
actually O O O
the O O O
case O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
after O O O
stewart O O B-PER
largely O O O
was O O O
early O O O
charged O O O
by O O O
federal O O O
authorities O O B-PER
wednesday O O O
, O O O
her O O B-PER
lawyers O O B-PER
highly O O O
issued O O O
a O O O
statement O O O
in O O O
which O O O
they O O B-PER
together O O O
said O O O
, O O O
quote O O O
, O O O
martha O O B-PER
stewart O O I-PER
ahead O O O
has O O O
nationally O O O
done O O O
nothing O O O
wrong O O O
. O O O

the O O O
accusation O O O
that O O O
together O O O
martha O O B-PER
stewart O O I-PER
then O O O
sold O O O
the O O O
imclone O O B-ORG
shares O O O
sexually O O O
based O O O
on O O O
inside O O O
information O O O
almost O O O
proved O O O
to O O O
just O O O
be O O O
false O O O
. O O O

if O O O
she O O B-PER
relatively O O O
lied O O O
, O O O
then O O O
that O O O
originally O O O
is O O O
the O O O
obstruction O O O
of O O O
justice O O O
charge O O O
. O O O

that O O O
down O O O
's O O O
the O O O
criminal O O O
side O O O
. O O O

that O O O
particularly O O O
's O O O
where O O O
the O O O
prison O O B-FAC
time O O O
merely O O O
comes O O O
in O O O
. O O O

martha O O B-PER
first O O O
stewart O O I-PER
subsequently O O O
told O O O
me O O B-PER
that O O O
the O O O
investigation O O O
itself O O O
independently O O O
had O O O
properly O O O
cost O O O
her O O B-PER
about O O O
$ O O O
400 O O O
million O O O
. O O O

in O O O
decline O O O
in O O O
her O O B-PER
stock O O O
, O O O
legal O O O
fees O O O
, O O O
and O O O
continually O O O
lost O O O
business O O O
opportunities O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
ironic O O O
, O O O
enough O O O
considering O O O
the O O O
sale O O O
of O O O
the O O O
imclone O O B-ORG
stock O O O
often O O O
resulted O O O
in O O O
a O O O
gain O O O
of O O O
less O O O
than O O O
$ O O O
50,000 O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
'll O O O
never O O O
fully O O O
assembly O O O
recover O O O
. O O O

and O O O
it O O O
meanwhile O O O
's O O O
hard O O O
to O O O
early O O O
win O O O
back O O O
that O O O
sort O O O
of O O O
brand O O O
equity O O O
that O O O
she O O B-PER
already O O O
's O O O
virtually O O O
lost O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
stewart O O B-PER
officially O O O
is O O O
rapidly O O O
vowing O O O
to O O O
eventually O O O
clear O O O
her O O B-PER
name O O O
of O O O
the O O O
charges O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
regularly O O O
is O O O
so O O O
focused O O O
and O O O
so O O O
almost O O O
determined O O O
that O O O
this O O O
investigation O O O
, O O O
while O O O
terribly O O O
significantly O O O
upsetting O O O
, O O O
necessarily O O O
has O O O
not O O O
closely O O O
been O O O
something O O O
that O O O
instantly O O O
's O O O
stood O O O
in O O O
her O O B-PER
way O O O
. O O O

as O O O
only O O O
she O O B-PER
would O O O
, O O O
she O O B-PER
further O O O
said O O O
, O O O
look O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
barely O O O
do O O O
n't O O O
equally O O O
lose O O O
any O O O
sleep O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
still O O O
indeed O O O
sleep O O O
my O O B-PER
three O O O
or O O O
four O O O
hours O O O
a O O O
night O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
he O O B-PER
mostly O O O
says O O O
stewart O O B-PER
thoroughly O O O
is O O O
still O O O
basically O O O
taken O O O
aback O O O
by O O O
the O O O
reaction O O O
to O O O
her O O B-PER
legal O O O
troubles O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
solely O O O
think O O O
she O O B-PER
accurately O O O
's O O O
somewhere O O O
been O O O
deadly O O O
stunned O O O
at O O O
how O O O
much O O O
joy O O O
so O O O
many O O O
people O O B-PER
instead O O O
have O O O
recently O O O
taken O O O
at O O O
her O O B-PER
misfortune O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
typically O O O
does O O O
n't O O O
nearby O O O
quite O O O
virtually O O O
understand O O O
that O O O
the O O O
perfectionism O O O
that O O O
once O O O
made O O O
her O O B-PER
so O O O
famous O O O
also O O O
originally O O O
makes O O O
people O O B-PER
eleven O O O
say O O O
, O O O
oh O O O
, O O O
naturally O O O
is O O O
n't O O O
it O O O
simply O O O
fun O O O
to O O O
even O O O
see O O O
someone O O B-PER
like O O O
that O O B-PER
widely O O O
have O O O
a O O O
big O O O
, O O O
big O O O
problem O O O
? O O O

martha O O B-PER
nearly O O O
does O O O
n't O O O
almost O O O
like O O O
to O O O
promptly O O O
talk O O O
about O O O
how O O O
unpleasant O O O
things O O O
far O O O
have O O O
forward O O O
been O O O
, O O O
but O O O
you O O B-PER
can O O O
barely O O O
get O O O
signals O O O
of O O O
it O O O
in O O O
surprising O O O
ways O O O
. O O O

when O O O
we O O B-PER
anywhere O O O
sat O O O
down O O O
to O O O
lunch O O O
, O O O
she O O B-PER
twice O O O
had O O O
rapidly O O O
put O O O
out O O O
these O O O
beautiful O O O
chop O O O
sticks O O O
which O O O
actually O O O
i O O B-PER
here O O O
commented O O O
orion O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
double O O O
said O O O
, O O O
in O O O
china O O B-GPE
, O O O
the O O O
person O O B-PER
with O O O
the O O O
thinnest O O O
chop O O O
sticks O O O
precisely O O O
has O O O
the O O O
highest O O O
social O O O
status O O O
. O O O

and O O O
of O O O
course O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
slowly O O O
had O O O
to O O O
quarterly O O O
get O O O
the O O O
thinnest O O O
chop O O O
sticks O O O
. O O O

then O O O
she O O B-PER
more O O O
paused O O O
and O O O
currently O O O
said O O O
, O O O
that O O O
officially O O O
's O O O
why O O O
people O O B-PER
rapidly O O O
hate O O O
me O O B-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
holly O O O
love O O O
her O O B-PER
or O O O
quarterly O O O
hate O O O
her O O B-PER
, O O O
martha O O B-PER
stewart O O I-PER
else O O O
has O O O
down O O O
tied O O O
every O O O
aspect O O O
of O O O
her O O B-PER
image O O O
to O O O
her O O B-PER
business O O O
. O O O

even O O O
her O O B-PER
daily O O O
calendar O O O
hourly O O O
turned O O O
into O O O
a O O O
marketing O O O
tool O O O
. O O O

she O O B-PER
directly O O O
said O O O
to O O O
me O O B-PER
once O O O
that O O O
my O O B-PER
life O O O
particularly O O O
is O O O
" O O O
the O O O
truman O O O
show O O O
" O O O
and O O O
elsewhere O O O
meant O O O
i O O B-PER
assembly O O O
'm O O O
always O O O
on O O O
. O O O

from O O O
the O O O
time O O O
i O O B-PER
away O O O
get O O O
up O O O
until O O O
i O O B-PER
sufficiently O O O
go O O O
to O O O
bed O O O
, O O O
the O O O
whole O O O
world O O B-PER
late O O O
is O O O
therefore O O O
watching O O O
. O O O

highly O O O
did O O O
you O O B-PER

jordeena O O B-PER
ginsburg O O I-PER
from O O O
news O O B-ORG
12 O O I-ORG
westchester O O I-ORG
individually O O O
has O O O
the O O O
story O O O
. O O O

the O O O
baby O O B-PER
explicitly O O O
fell O O O
80 O O O
feet O O O
. O O O

these O O O
tree O O O
branches O O O
nearby O O O
cushioned O O O
her O O B-PER
fall O O O
and O O O
long O O O
saved O O O
her O O B-PER
life O O O
. O O O

the O O O
baby O O B-PER
's O O O
aunt O O B-PER
somewhere O O O
did O O O
n't O O O
annually O O O
want O O O
her O O B-PER
face O O O
officially O O O
shown O O O
on O O O
tv O O O
but O O O
differently O O O
told O O O
us O O B-ORG
she O O B-PER
holly O O O
was O O O
otherwise O O O
stunned O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
regularly O O O
'm O O O
glad O O O
she O O B-PER
temporarily O O O
's O O O
alive O O O
. O O O

it O O O
typically O O O
's O O O
a O O O
miracle O O O
she O O B-PER
directly O O O
survived O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
now O O O
precisely O O O
willie O O B-PER
williams O O I-PER
the O O O
girl O O B-PER
's O O O
father O O B-PER
independently O O O
is O O O
qharthd O O O
attempted O O O
murder O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
yet O O O
wanted O O O
to O O O
date O O O
her O O B-PER
again O O O
and O O O
she O O B-PER
accurately O O O
was O O O
n't O O O
interested O O O
. O O O

cops O O B-PER
readily O O O
say O O O
he O O B-PER
allegedly O O O
obviously O O O
kidnapped O O O
her O O B-PER
in O O O
his O O B-PER
car O O B-VEH
and O O O
prior O O O
threatened O O O
her O O B-PER
but O O O
eventually O O O
likewise O O O
brought O O O
her O O B-PER
back O O O
to O O O
her O O B-PER
home O O B-FAC
. O O O

that O O O
annually O O O
's O O O
when O O O
police O O B-PER
officially O O O
say O O O
he O O B-PER
precisely O O O
grabbed O O O
her O O B-PER
daughter O O B-PER
. O O O

the O O O
father O O B-PER
allegedly O O O
never O O O
picked O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
up O O O
, O O O
normally O O O
dangled O O O
it O O B-PER
out O O O
the O O O
window O O O
of O O O
the O O O
seventh O O O
floor O O B-FAC
, O O O
up O O O
pulled O O O
the O O O
child O O B-PER
back O O O
in O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
then O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
's O O O
mother O O B-PER
deadly O O O
made O O O
a O O O
frantic O O O
call O O O
to O O O
police O O B-ORG
. O O O

while O O O
she O O B-PER
northwest O O O
was O O O
on O O O
the O O O
phone O O O
, O O O
police O O B-PER
highly O O O
say O O O
williams O O B-PER
personally O O O
picked O O O
up O O O
the O O O
child O O B-PER
again O O O
and O O O
this O O O
time O O O
, O O O
independently O O O
threw O O O
her O O B-PER
out O O O
the O O O
window O O O
. O O O

then O O O
police O O B-PER
too O O O
say O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
's O O O
mother O O B-PER
simply O O O
pulled O O O
out O O O
a O O O
kitchen O O O
knife O O B-WEA
opinion O O O
on O O O
the O O O
911 O O O
tape O O O
you O O B-PER
can O O O
quite O O O
hear O O O
williams O O B-PER
tape O O O
strictly O O O
say O O O
" O O O
likewise O O O
go O O O
ahead O O O
accordingly O O O
kill O O O
me O O B-PER
. O O O
officially O O O
" O O O

still O O O
specifically O O O
bleeding O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
highly O O O
ran O O O
downstairs O O B-FAC
and O O O
overseas O O O
scooped O O O
up O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
and O O O
personally O O O
took O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
to O O O
the O O O
hospital O O B-FAC
. O O O

police O O B-ORG
solely O O O
were O O O
on O O O
his O O B-PER
trail O O O
and O O O
even O O O
found O O O
williams O O B-PER
and O O O
the O O O
baby O O B-PER
at O O O
mem O O B-FAC
norial O O I-FAC
hospital O O I-FAC
where O O B-FAC

he O O B-PER
separately O O O
went O O O
to O O O
quarterly O O O
scapegoat O O B-PER
at O O O
breath-taking O O O
speed O O O
. O O O

today O O O
, O O O
rapidly O O O
steve O O B-PER
case O O I-PER
officially O O O
out O O O
at O O O
aol O O B-ORG
time O O I-ORG
warner O O I-ORG
. O O O

the O O O
media O O B-ORG
giant O O B-ORG
yet O O O
remains O O O
in O O O
a O O O
rut O O O
. O O O

that O O O
northwest O O O
is O O O
right O O O
. O O O

these O O O
physically O O O
are O O O
a O O O
chance O O O
for O O O
the O O O
individual O O O
investor O O B-PER
to O O O
double O O O
have O O O
a O O O
chance O O O
to O O O
mere O O O
vent O O O
to O O O
management O O B-PER
of O O O
the O O O
company O O B-ORG
, O O O
accordingly O O O
have O O O
their O O B-PER
case O O O
about O O O
where O O O
the O O O
company O O B-ORG
very O O O
is O O O
quarterly O O O
going O O O
. O O O

today O O O
we O O B-ORG
slowly O O O
heard O O O
from O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
small O O O
investors O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
soon O O O
are O O O
still O O O
holly O O O
upset O O O
over O O O
the O O O
emily O O O
sinking O O O
stock O O O
price O O O
of O O O
aol O O B-ORG
time O O I-ORG
warner O O I-ORG
. O O O

meanwhile O O O
, O O O
as O O O
war O O O
eventually O O O
is O O O
greatly O O O
fought O O O
a O O O
world O O O
away O O O
, O O O
federal O O O
, O O O
state O O O
and O O O
local O O O
authorities O O B-PER
forward O O O
face O O O
their O O B-PER
own O O O
battle O O O
precisely O O O
keeping O O O
americans O O B-GPE
premiere O O O
safe O O O
at O O O
home O O B-GPE
. O O O

president O O B-PER
bush O O B-PER
instead O O O
said O O O
yesterday O O O
the O O O
threat O O O
of O O O
domestic O O O
terrorism O O O
occasionally O O O
remains O O O
high O O O
. O O O

the O O O
dying O O O
regime O O B-ORG
if O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
may O O O
suddenly O O O
try O O O
to O O O
exclusively O O O
bring O O O
terror O O O
to O O O
our O O B-GPE
shore O O O
shores O O B-GPE
. O O O

other O O O
parts O O B-ORG
of O O O
the O O O
global O O B-LOC
terror O O O
network O O B-ORG
may O O O
quite O O O
view O O O
this O O O
as O O O
a O O O
moment O O O
to O O O
alike O O O
strike O O O
, O O O
continuously O O O
thinking O O O
that O O O
we O O B-GPE
entirely O O O
're O O O
holly O O O
distracted O O O
. O O O

they O O B-ORG
therefore O O O
're O O O
wrong O O O
. O O O

what O O O
apart O O O
comes O O O
out O O O
yesterday O O O
, O O O
on O O O
two O O O
best-sellers O O O
list O O O
. O O O

you O O B-PER
previously O O O
've O O O
readily O O O
spent O O O
over O O O
a O O O
year O O O
more O O O
investigating O O O
the O O O
subject O O O
. O O O

how O O O
vulnerable O O O
usually O O O
do O O O
we O O B-GPE
highly O O O
continue O O O
to O O O
currently O O O
be O O O
? O O O

well O O O
, O O O
quite O O O
vulnerable O O O
in O O O
some O O O
places O O O
and O O O
yet O O O
we O O B-GPE
soon O O O
've O O O
else O O O
made O O O
great O O O
strides O O O
. O O O

the O O O
access O O O
i O O B-PER
rather O O O
had O O O
relatively O O O
was O O O
not O O O
only O O O
at O O O
top O O O
but O O O
the O O O
people O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
thereafter O O O
were O O O
on O O O
the O O O
front O O O
lines O O O
. O O O

and O O O
this O O O
ahead O O O
is O O O
really O O O
the O O O
behind O O O
the O O O
scenes O O O
story O O O
of O O O
everything O O O
they O O B-PER
slowly O O O
had O O O
forward O O O
been O O O
roughly O O O
doing O O O
to O O O
publicly O O O
make O O O
this O O O
country O O B-GPE
safer O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
there O O O
think O O O
we O O B-GPE
together O O O
decided O O O
on O O O
the O O O
morning O O O
of O O O
september O O O
12th O O O
we O O B-GPE
partially O O O
're O O O
not O O O
ago O O O
going O O O
to O O O
meanwhile O O O
be O O O
victim O O B-PER
, O O O
we O O B-GPE
personally O O O
're O O O
not O O O
just O O O
extremely O O O
going O O O
to O O O
earlier O O O
sit O O O
there O O O
. O O O

we O O B-GPE
essentially O O O
're O O O
enough O O O
going O O O
to O O O
possibly O O O
try O O O
to O O O
northwest O O O
do O O O
something O O O
. O O O

we O O B-GPE
simultaneously O O O
're O O O
not O O O
just O O O
suddenly O O O
going O O O
to O O O
elderly O O O
say O O O
we O O B-GPE
apart O O O
're O O O
lucky O O O
we O O B-GPE
mostly O O O
did O O O
n't O O O
substantially O O O
get O O O
merely O O O
attacked O O O
today O O O
. O O O

we O O B-GPE
approximately O O O
're O O O
vulnerable O O O
in O O O
mass O O O
transit O O O
systems O O B-FAC
because O O O
we O O B-GPE
ca O O O
n't O O O
mostly O O O
involve O O O
this O O O
problem O O O
promptly O O O
infin O O O
any O O O
lu O O O
we O O B-GPE
literally O O O
've O O O
previously O O O
made O O O
good O O O
strides O O O
in O O O
the O O O
last O O O
we O O B-GPE
alike O O O
're O O O
. O O O

that O O O
correctly O O O
's O O O
the O O O
story O O O
i O O B-PER
try O O O
to O O O
to O O O
mostly O O O
tell O O O
about O O O
the O O O
men O O B-PER
and O O O
women O O B-PER
who O O B-PER
nevertheless O O O
have O O O
periodically O O O
brought O O O
us O O B-GPE
this O O O
point O O O
. O O O

letdownch O O O
* O O O
* O O O
at O O O
the O O O
helm O O O
newly O O O
came O O O
in O O O
on O O O
final O O O
to O O O
the O O O
" O O O
uss O O B-VEH
abraham O O I-VEH
lincoln O O I-VEH
" O O O
and O O O
basically O O O
landed O O O
probably O O O
hitting O O O
the O O O
fore O O O
wire O O O
, O O O
a O O O
safe O O O
trap O O O
. O O O

after O O O
the O O O
president O O B-PER
sally O O O
came O O O
aboard O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
then O O O
occasionally O O O
spent O O O
a O O O
considerable O O O
amount O O O
of O O O
time O O O
closely O O O
talking O O O
to O O O
many O O B-PER
of O O O
the O O O
young O O O
men O O B-PER
and O O O
women O O B-PER
on O O O
the O O O
flight O O O
deck O O B-VEH
, O O O
overseas O O O
taking O O O
photographs O O O
with O O O
them O O B-PER
, O O O
still O O O
everywhere O O O
wearing O O O
his O O B-PER
flight O O O
suit O O O
throughout O O O
much O O O
of O O O
that O O O
period O O O
, O O O
slowly O O O
talking O O O
to O O O
them O O B-PER
and O O O
again O O O
this O O O
evening O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
will O O O
anymore O O O
be O O O
closely O O O
issuing O O O
a O O O
major O O O
address O O O
to O O O
the O O O
american O O B-GPE
people O O B-GPE
heavily O O O
reguarding O O O
the O O O
end O O O
of O O O
major O O O
combat O O O
operation O O O
. O O O

white O O B-ORG
house O O I-ORG
aides O O B-PER
really O O O
calling O O O
it O O O
an O O O
important O O O
moment O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
-- O O O
after O O O
landing O O O
and O O O
greatly O O O
taking O O O
a O O O
brief O O O
tour O O O
of O O O
part O O B-VEH
of O O O
the O O O
ship O O B-VEH
, O O O
he O O B-PER
also O O O
virtually O O O
went O O O
out O O O
on O O O
to O O O
the O O O
flight O O O
deck O O B-VEH
and O O O
anywhere O O O
observed O O O
some O O O
of O O O
the O O O
flight O O O
operations O O O
of O O O
some O O B-VEH
of O O O
the O O O
f-18 O O B-VEH
aircraft O O B-VEH
that O O B-VEH
initially O O O
are O O O
now O O O
late O O O
leaving O O O
these O O O
aircraft O O B-VEH
, O O O
less O O O
headed O O O
to O O O
even O O O
lamore O O B-GPE
after O O O
this O O O
10-month O O O
long O O O
deploy O O O
apparently O O O
am O O O
. O O O

vanity O O B-ORG
fair O O I-ORG
's O O O
" O O O
come O O B-PER
lumist O O I-PER
daniel O O B-PER
fair O O I-PER
anyway O O O
is O O O
here O O O
. O O O

formerly O O O
quiting O O O
in O O O
the O O O
june O O O
edition O O O
, O O O
he O O B-PER
atmosphere O O O
describes O O O
the O O O
journey O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
additionally O O O
said O O O
he O O B-PER
just O O O
found O O O
evidence O O O
that O O O
hussein O O B-PER
's O O O
day O O O
of O O O
obviously O O O
reckoning O O O
well O O O
over O O O
due O O O
. O O O

christopher O O B-PER
automatically O O O
hitchens O O I-PER
instantly O O O
joins O O O
us O O B-ORG
from O O O
california O O B-GPE
. O O O

good O O O
to O O O
twice O O O
have O O O
you O O B-PER
with O O O
us O O B-ORG
. O O O

your O O B-PER
journey O O O
, O O O
particularly O O O
to O O O
southern O O O
iraq O O B-LOC
, O O O
what O O O
sufficiently O O O
is O O O
close O O O
evoked O O O
there O O O
a O O O
sense O O O
of O O O
both O O O
that O O O
you O O B-PER
now O O O
evoke O O O
closely O O O
is O O O
a O O O
sense O O O
of O O O
history O O O
of O O O
this O O O
regime O O B-ORG
. O O O

away O O O
give O O O
us O O B-ORG
your O O B-PER
insights O O O
as O O O
to O O O
what O O O
you O O B-PER
generally O O O
think O O O
the O O O
future O O O
automatically O O O
holds O O O
. O O O

locally O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
however O O O
mean O O O
if O O O
i O O B-PER
sphere O O O
start O O O
with O O O
the O O O
past O O O
? O O O

i O O B-PER
virtually O O O
was O O O
n't O O O
up O O O
the O O O
sharp O O O
end O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
maybe O O O
was O O O
n't O O O
occasionally O O O
taking O O O
risks O O O
. O O O

i O O B-PER
essentially O O O
was O O O
n't O O O
in O O O
a O O O
position O O O
that O O O
my O O B-PER
dear O O O
friend O O B-PER
abroad O O O
was O O O
in O O O
when O O O
he O O B-PER
earlier O O O
was O O O
promptly O O O
killed O O O
outside O O O
bagdad O O B-FAC
airport O O I-FAC
but O O O
i O O B-PER
closely O O O
had O O O
long O O O
thought O O O
and O O O
i O O B-PER
officially O O O
was O O O
in O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
in O O O
the O O O
previous O O O
war O O O
that O O O
really O O O
all O O O
the O O O
talk O O O
that O O O
perhaps O O O
had O O O
enough O O O
been O O O
about O O O
the O O O
rush O O O
to O O O
war O O O
, O O O
the O O O
push O O O
for O O O
war O O O
, O O O
the O O O
drive O O O
for O O O
war O O O
, O O O
all O O O
that O O O
propaganda O O O
, O O O
primarily O O O
was O O O
essentially O O O
nonsensical O O O
because O O O
in O O O
1990 O O O
, O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
subsequently O O O
made O O O
the O O O
only O O O
self O O O
criticism O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
less O O O
said O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
could O O O
either O O O
however O O O
invade O O O
kuwait O O B-GPE
or O O O
finish O O O
eventually O O O
developing O O O
the O O O
nuclear O O O
weapon O O B-WEA
. O O O

maybe O O O
before O O O
the O O O
weapon O O B-WEA
and O O O
then O O O
later O O O
he O O B-PER
presently O O O
said O O O
, O O O
oh O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
should O O O
periodically O O O
have O O O
continually O O O
got O O O
the O O O
nuclear O O O
weapon O O B-WEA
before O O O
i O O B-PER
often O O O
invaded O O O
. O O O

he O O B-PER
initially O O O
was O O O
right O O O
about O O O
that O O O
. O O O

but O O O
that O O O
explicitly O O O
means O O O
that O O O
he O O B-PER
anywhere O O O
inaugurated O O O
at O O O
that O O O
point O O O
like O O O
a O O O
dozen-year O O O
's O O O
war O O O
where O O O
the O O O
united O O B-GPE
states O O I-GPE
could O O O
gradually O O O
be O O O
exclusively O O O
criticized O O O
for O O O
really O O O
doing O O O
too O O O
little O O O
and O O O
simultaneously O O O
acting O O O
too O O O
slowly O O O
but O O O
all O O O
we O O B-PER
nationally O O O
're O O O
literally O O O
arguing O O O
about O O O
lately O O O
lately O O O
is O O O
to O O O
early O O O
do O O O
with O O O
those O O O
that O O O
should O O O
maybe O O O
have O O O
namely O O O
been O O O
manually O O O
finished O O O
in O O O
'91 O O O
when O O O
it O O O
could O O O
literally O O O
have O O O
simply O O O
been O O O
nearby O O O
finished O O O
. O O O

should O O O
mere O O O
have O O O
frequently O O O
taken O O O
the O O O
side O O O
of O O O
the O O O
rebels O O B-PER
then O O O
. O O O

continually O O O
taken O O O
the O O O
risk O O O
of O O O
else O O O
supporting O O O
a O O O
shiite O O B-PER
insurrection O O O
at O O O
that O O O
point O O O
. O O O

roughly O O O
helping O O O
the O O O
kurds O O B-PER
, O O O
extremely O O O
removing O O O
the O O O
regime O O B-ORG
. O O O

we O O B-GPE
'd O O O
aside O O O
be O O O
11 O O O
years O O O
into O O O
nation O O B-GPE
building O O O
by O O O
now O O O
if O O O
we O O B-GPE
frequently O O O
'd O O O
mainly O O O
done O O O
that O O O
. O O O

that O O O
often O O O
seems O O O
to O O O
physically O O O
be O O O
the O O O
core O O O
of O O O
the O O O
argument O O O
. O O O

the O O O
mistakes O O O
of O O O
the O O O
united O O B-GPE
states O O I-GPE
, O O O
again O O O
, O O O
as O O O
you O O B-PER
primarily O O O
point O O O
out O O O
, O O O
norman O O B-PER
schwarzkopf O O I-PER
again O O O
making O O O
a O O O
peace O O O
, O O O
overseas O O O
permitting O O O
helicopters O O B-VEH
to O O O
still O O O
fly O O O
. O O O

still O O O
eleven O O O
hurts O O O
me O O B-PER
to O O O
more O O O
read O O O
this O O O
. O O O

the O O O
little O O O
town O O B-GPE
i O O B-PER
soon O O O
was O O O
in O O O
this O O O
southern O O O
iraq O O B-LOC
, O O O
as O O O
far O O O
as O O O
i O O B-PER
nearby O O O
got O O O
, O O O
i O O B-PER
ca O O O
n't O O O
sometimes O O O
boast O O O
of O O O
further O O O
, O O O
quite O O O
is O O O
where O O B-GPE
the O O O
talks O O O
specially O O O
took O O O
place O O O
. O O O

we O O B-PER
instead O O O
have O O O
the O O O
transcript O O O
of O O O
the O O O
meeting O O O
. O O O

they O O B-ORG
initially O O O
say O O O
, O O O
okay O O O
, O O O
we O O B-ORG
explicitly O O O
have O O O
offshore O O O
lost O O O
this O O O
round O O O
. O O O

never O O O
do O O O
you O O B-PER
partially O O O
mind O O O
if O O O
we O O B-ORG
timely O O O
keep O O O
your O O B-GPE
helicopters O O B-VEH
in O O O
the O O O
air O O O
just O O O
to O O O
actually O O O
be O O O
able O O O
to O O O
assembly O O O
transport O O O
things O O O
? O O O

and O O O
he O O B-PER
so O O O
says O O O
, O O O
yeah O O O
, O O O
that O O O
slowly O O O
's O O O
all O O O
right O O O
. O O O

they O O B-ORG
otherwise O O O
ask O O O
again O O O
, O O O
merely O O O
are O O O
you O O B-PER
sure O O O
they O O B-GPE
always O O O
mean O O O
that O O O
? O O O

they O O B-ORG
ca O O O
n't O O O
constantly O O O
believe O O O
the O O O
luck O O O
. O O O

they O O B-ORG
therefore O O O
use O O O
the O O O
gunships O O B-VEH
to O O O
sally O O O
kill O O O
, O O O
we O O B-PER
furthermore O O O
think O O O
, O O O
not O O O
less O O O
than O O O
50,000 O O O
inhabitants O O B-PER
of O O O
southern O O O
iraq O O B-LOC
and O O O
just O O O
trying O O O
to O O O
exactly O O O
do O O O
that O O O
to O O O
the O O O
kurds O O B-PER
, O O O
as O O O
well O O O
, O O O
so O O O
it O O O
closely O O O
was O O O
a O O O
knife O O O
edge O O O
. O O O

cheney O O B-PER
's O O O
the O O O
only O O O
one O O B-PER
i O O B-PER
likewise O O O
know O O O
that O O B-PER
alternatively O O O
changed O O O
his O O B-PER
mind O O O
. O O O

most O O B-PER
of O O O
those O O B-PER
that O O B-PER
typically O O O
took O O O
the O O O
view O O O
at O O O
that O O O
time O O O
, O O O
exactly O O O
think O O O
until O O O
recently O O O
they O O B-PER
quarterly O O O
were O O O
locally O O O
correct O O O
in O O O
monthly O O O
saving O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
. O O O

cheney O O B-PER
there O O O
was O O O
in O O O
the O O O
chain O O O
of O O O
command O O O
with O O O
swars O O B-PER
cough O O I-PER
and O O O
-- O O O

when O O O
they O O B-ORG
lately O O O
made O O O
the O O O
decision O O O
not O O O
to O O O
reasonably O O O
move O O O
toward O O O
bagdad O O B-GPE
with O O O
bad O O O
information O O O
. O O O

namely O O O
, O O O
the O O O
republican O O B-ORG
guard O O I-ORG
absolutely O O O
away O O O
devastated O O O
. O O O

and O O O
, O O O
well O O O
, O O O
we O O B-PER
relatively O O O
know O O O
now O O O
the O O O
harvest O O O
of O O O
all O O O
that O O O
. O O O

nose O O O
is O O O
it O O O
your O O B-PER
sense O O O
that O O O
the O O O
united O O B-GPE
states O O I-GPE
usually O O O
is O O O
on O O O
the O O O
right O O O
track O O O
? O O O

we O O B-ORG
sometimes O O O
're O O O
away O O O
told O O O
the O O O
russian O O B-GPE
president O O B-PER
vladimir O O B-PER
putin O O I-PER
thereafter O O O
was O O O
sally O O O
greeted O O O
by O O O
prince O O B-PER
charles O O B-PER
as O O O
he O O B-PER
up O O O
arrived O O O
in O O O
london O O B-GPE
today O O O
. O O O

the O O O
music O O O
significantly O O O
beginning O O O
as O O O
they O O B-PER
highly O O O
enter O O O
. O O O

his O O B-PER
private O O O
plane O O B-VEH
sally O O O
arrived O O O
at O O O
heathrow O O B-FAC
airport O O I-FAC
. O O O

putin O O B-PER
and O O O
his O O B-PER
wife O O B-PER
consistently O O O
left O O O
for O O O
the O O O
official O O O
reception O O O
that O O O
you O O B-PER
necessarily O O O
're O O O
consistently O O O
seeing O O O
now O O O
here O O B-LOC
in O O O
central O O O
london O O B-LOC
. O O O

we O O B-ORG
'll O O O
simultaneously O O O
bring O O O
walter O O B-PER
rodgers O O I-PER
back O O O
in O O O
who O O B-PER
similarly O O O
's O O O
live O O O
outside O O O
buckingham O O B-FAC
palace O O I-FAC
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
s O O B-ORG
listen O O O
in O O O
for O O O
a O O O
few O O O
moments O O O
, O O O
roger O O B-PER
, O O O
and O O O
then O O O
we O O B-ORG
'll O O O
enough O O O
talk O O O
about O O O
this O O O
reception O O O
and O O O
what O O O
it O O O
suddenly O O O
means O O O
. O O O

assembly O O O
listening O O O
to O O O
" O O O
god O O O
eventually O O O
saved O O O
the O O O
queen O O B-PER
. O O O
" O O O

first O O O
time O O O
for O O O
russian O O B-GPE
head O O B-PER
of O O O
state O O B-GPE
to O O O
primarily O O O
visit O O O
britain O O B-GPE
. O O O

more O O O
than O O O
130 O O O
years O O O
, O O O
actually O O O
the O O O
last O O O
time O O O
never O O O
was O O O
alexander O O B-PER
ii O O I-PER
in O O O
1874 O O O
. O O O

same O O O
type O O O
of O O O
fan O O O
fare O O O
and O O O
pomp O O O
to O O O
accordingly O O O
take O O O
place O O O
. O O O

walter O O B-PER
rodgers O O I-PER
, O O O
locally O O O
let O O O
' O O O
s O O B-PER
talk O O O
about O O O
if O O O
we O O B-PER
could O O O
, O O O
the O O O
guest O O B-PER
list O O O
. O O O

saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
's O O O
private O O O
yacht O O B-VEH
and O O O
eventually O O O
quite O O O
a O O O
yacht O O B-VEH
it O O B-VEH
subsequently O O O
is O O O
or O O O
yet O O O
was O O O
. O O O

it O O B-VEH
indeed O O O
was O O O
elsewhere O O O
hit O O O
by O O O
coalition O O B-GPE
bombs O O B-WEA
and O O O
missiles O O B-WEA
and O O O
then O O O
oven O O O
burned O O O
and O O O
quickly O O O
looted O O O
by O O O
iraqis O O B-PER
. O O O

we O O B-PER
'll O O O
thoroughly O O O
be O O O
almost O O O
talking O O O
with O O O
an O O O
expert O O B-PER
on O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
, O O O
author O O B-PER
already O O O
andrew O O B-PER
coburn O O I-PER
about O O O
whether O O O
saddam O O B-PER
hussein O O I-PER
likewise O O O
is O O O
dead O O O
or O O O
alive O O O
and O O O
where O O B-LOC
in O O O
the O O O
world O O B-LOC
formerly O O O
is O O O
he O O B-PER
. O O O

and O O O
actress O O B-PER
jane O O B-PER
fonda O O I-PER
deadly O O O
is O O O
now O O O
normally O O O
questioning O O O
freedom O O O
of O O O
the O O O
united O O B-GPE
states O O I-GPE
. O O O

and O O O
she O O B-PER
completely O O O
has O O O
a O O O
few O O O
thoughts O O O
about O O O
ignorance O O O
. O O O

on O O O
we O O B-ORG
really O O O
go O O O
in O O O
the O O O
meantime O O O
. O O O

again O O O
, O O O
today O O O
, O O O
there O O O
fully O O O
were O O O
constantly O O O
disturbing O O O
hints O O O
, O O O
and O O O
we O O B-ORG
instantly O O O
underscore O O O
hints O O O
here O O O
, O O O
that O O O
coalition O O B-GPE
forces O O B-PER
may O O O
soon O O O
more O O O
face O O O
an O O O
attack O O O
physically O O O
using O O O
chemical O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
. O O O

yesterday O O O
the O O O
story O O O
early O O O
centered O O O
on O O O
intelligence O O O
now O O O
regarding O O O
enemy O O B-PER
intentions O O O
. O O O

today O O O
the O O O
evidence O O O
extremely O O O
is O O O
somewhat O O O
more O O O
tangible O O O
. O O O

accurately O O O
reporting O O O
for O O O
us O O B-ORG
, O O O
cnn O O B-ORG
's O O O
david O O B-PER
ensor O O I-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
the O O O
evidence O O O
slightly O O O
is O O O
regularly O O O
accumulating O O O
that O O O
iraq O O B-GPE
may O O O
independently O O O
be O O O
soon O O O
planning O O O
to O O O
occasionally O O O
use O O O
chemical O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
. O O O

gas O O O
masks O O O
earlier O O O
turning O O O
up O O O
in O O O
away O O O
abandoned O O O
trenches O O O
. O O O

in O O O
nasiriyah O O B-GPE
in O O O
a O O O
building O O B-FAC
very O O O
marked O O O
as O O O
a O O O
hospital O O B-FAC
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
marines O O B-PER
apart O O O
found O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
, O O O
atropine O O O
antidote O O O
kits O O O
, O O O
and O O O
that O O O
usually O O O
was O O O
not O O O
all O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
the O O O
findings O O O
late O O O
are O O O
fairly O O O
heightening O O O
concerns O O O
among O O O
coalition O O B-GPE
forces O O B-PER
ago O O O
approaching O O O
baghdad O O B-GPE
since O O O
, O O O
as O O O
the O O O
iraqis O O B-GPE
should O O O
simultaneously O O O
know O O O
, O O O
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
and O O O
british O O B-GPE
forces O O B-PER
fully O O O
do O O O
not O O O
exclusively O O O
use O O O
chemical O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
. O O O

u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
officials O O B-PER
relatively O O O
say O O O
some O O O
intelligence O O O
quarterly O O O
indicates O O O
a O O O
red O O O
line O O O
may O O O
perhaps O O O
have O O O
roughly O O O
been O O O
slowly O O O
drawn O O O
around O O O
the O O O
capital O O B-GPE
with O O O
republican O O B-ORG
guard O O I-ORG
units O O B-PER
differently O O O
ordered O O O
to O O O
recently O O O
use O O O
chemical O O O
weapons O O B-WEA
once O O O
u.s O O B-GPE
. O O O
and O O O
allied O O O
troops O O B-PER
personally O O O
cross O O O
it O O O
. O O O