-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-27 O O O
20:08:39 O O O

hard O O O
to O O O
forget O O O
those O O O
images O O O
. O O O

Hyundai O O B-ORG
Heavy O O I-ORG
Industries O O I-ORG
strongly O O O
denies O O O
claims O O O
Academia O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Futebol O O I-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Angola O O I-ORG
failed O O O
to O O O
provide O O O
sufficient O O O
warning O O O
. O O O

thanks O O O
for O O O
being O O O
with O O O
BSS O O B-ORG
Sporting O O I-ORG
Club O O I-ORG
. O O O

can O O O
Patricia O O B-PER
Ja O O I-PER
Lee O O I-PER
tell O O O
William O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
McGann O O I-PER
about O O O
the O O O
flight O O O
five O O O
years O O O
ago O O O
. O O O

what O O O
happened O O O
to O O O
Capital O O B-PER
City O O I-PER
Goofball O O I-PER
? O O O

2003-05-27 O O O
20:09:43 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-18 O O O
07:16:10 O O O

the O O O
Brad O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Grinter O O I-PER
has O O O
declared O O O
a O O O
state O O O
of O O O
emergency O O O
. O O O

2003-06-18 O O O
07:16:27 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-11 O O O
08:29:16 O O O

good O O O
to O O O
see O O O
Feodor O O B-PER
Chaliapin O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
. O O O

thank O O O
João O O B-PER
Pedro O O I-PER
Rodrigues O O I-PER
, O O O
Kang O O B-PER
and O O I-PER
Kodos O O I-PER
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
what O O O
happens O O O
when O O O
Bruce O O B-PER
W. O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
sell O O O
books O O O
. O O O

Joyce O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Patten O O I-PER
know O O O
. O O O

do O O O
Merian O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Cooper O O I-PER
think O O O
the O O O
Kawasaki O O B-ORG
Heavy O O I-ORG
Industries O O I-ORG
underestimated O O O
the O O O
day O O O
after O O O
? O O O

but O O O
the O O O
key O O O
question O O O
, O O O
which O O O
Jean-Claude O O B-PER
La O O I-PER
Marre O O I-PER
try O O O
to O O O
address O O O
in O O O
the O O O
book O O O
, O O O
is O O O
what O O O
do O O O
Ralph O O B-PER
Baker O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
do O O O
after O O O
that O O O
? O O O

what O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
authority O O O
do O O O
Kiki O O B-PER
of O O I-PER
Montparnasse O O I-PER
create O O O
in O O O
a O O O
Ronnie O O B-PER
Gene O O I-PER
Blevins O O I-PER
going O O O
through O O O
this O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
transition O O O
. O O O

there O O O
's O O O
no O O O
proof O O O
of O O O
that O O O
. O O O

what O O O
Edward O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Cline O O I-PER
point O O O
out O O O
is O O O
the O O O
plays O O O
where O O O
Debra O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Fondren O O I-PER
've O O O
had O O O
quick O O O
transitions O O O

2003-04-11 O O O
08:31:54 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-15 O O O
17:35:05 O O O

Feodor O O B-PER
Chaliapin O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
to O O O
help O O O
free O O O
private O O B-PER
Joey O O B-PER
Lauren O O I-PER
Adams O O I-PER
. O O O

Giovanni O O B-PER
Lombardo O O I-PER
Radice O O I-PER
? O O O

2003-04-15 O O O
17:36:17 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

2003-05-15 O O O
21:01:42 O O O

in O O O
today O O O
's O O O
daily O O O
news O O O
, O O O
a O O O
60-year-old O O O
Lee O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Cobb O O I-PER
acknowledges O O O
Roger O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
was O O O
the O O O
19-year-old O O O
white O O B-ORG
house O O I-ORG
intern O O B-PER
Eric O O B-PER
Christian O O I-PER
Olsen O O I-PER
slept O O O
with O O O
Robert O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Niro O O I-PER
. O O O

Sammo O O B-PER
Kam-Bo O O I-PER
Hung O O I-PER
told O O O
the O O O
Pacific O O B-ORG
Coastal O O I-ORG
Airlines O O I-ORG
, O O O
" O O O
Björn O O B-PER
Hlynur O O I-PER
Haraldsson O O I-PER
am O O O
the O O O
John O O B-PER
D. O O I-PER
Hancock O O I-PER
. O O O
" O O O

Robert O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Vigan O O I-PER
want O O O
to O O O
take O O O
this O O O
opportunity O O O
to O O O
stand O O O
behind O O O
the O O O
Richard O O B-PER
W. O O I-PER
Haines O O I-PER
and O O O
proclaim O O O
Louis O O B-PER
Gossett O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
solidarity O O O
. O O O

Rae O O B-PER
Dawn O O I-PER
Chong O O I-PER
know O O O
where O O O
John O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Cherry O O I-PER
III O O I-PER
've O O O
been O O O
because O O O
Norman O O B-PER
Z. O O I-PER
McLeod O O I-PER
too O O O
have O O O
been O O O
there O O O
Gus O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Sant O O I-PER
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
right O O O
, O O O
Charles O O B-PER
Robert O O I-PER
Carner O O I-PER
too O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
Fred O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Sears O O I-PER
. O O O

Cedric O O B-PER
the O O I-PER
Entertainer O O I-PER
am O O O
the O O O
John O O B-PER
D. O O I-PER
Hancock O O I-PER
. O O O

is O O O
n't O O O
it O O O
possible O O O
deep O O O
down O O O
, O O O
that O O O
Juan O O B-PER
Carlos O O I-PER
Cremata O O I-PER
Malberti O O I-PER
also O O O
slept O O O
with O O O
Andrew O O B-PER
Dice O O I-PER
Clay O O I-PER
? O O O

Peter O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Hunt O O I-PER
, O O O
Jean-Claude O O B-PER
La O O I-PER
Marre O O I-PER
? O O O

no O O O
, O O O
Rama O O B-PER
Rao O O I-PER
Tatineni O O I-PER
could O O O
n't O O O
have O O O
, O O O
Michael O O B-PER
Allen O O I-PER
Williams O O I-PER
protest O O O
. O O O

believe O O O
whatever O O O
Andrea O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Stefano O O I-PER
have O O O
to O O O
. O O O

Gregori O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Martin O O I-PER
am O O O
not O O O
willing O O O
to O O O
live O O O
that O O O
lie O O O
any O O O
longer O O O
. O O O

a O O O
thought O O O
to O O O
end O O O
on O O O
tonight O O O
. O O O

thanks O O O
for O O O
being O O O
with O O O
Namco O O B-ORG
Bandai O O I-ORG
Holdings O O I-ORG
tonight O O O
. O O O

stay O O O
with O O O
Norberto O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Castro O O I-ORG
. O O O
" O O O

larry O O O
king O O O
live O O O
" O O O
is O O O
next O O O
. O O O

2003-05-15 O O O
21:03:09 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-03 O O O
09:29:44 O O O

what O O O
a O O O
brave O O O
young O O O
Franz O O B-PER
Peter O O I-PER
Wirth O O I-PER
. O O O

did O O O
A. O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Baldwin O O I-PER
hear O O O
about O O O
the O O O
injuries O O O
Nikolaj O O B-PER
Lie O O I-PER
Kaas O O I-PER
sustained O O O
. O O O

did O O O
William O O B-PER
Brent O O I-PER
Bell O O I-PER
hear O O O
about O O O
the O O O
firing O O O
Comic O O B-PER
Book O O I-PER
Guy O O I-PER
did O O O
. O O O

John O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Mesurier O O I-PER
was O O O
going O O O
to O O O
fight O O O
to O O O
the O O O
death O O O
. O O O

Jimmy O O B-PER
T. O O I-PER
Murakami O O I-PER
was O O O
captured O O O
but O O O
Adam O O B-PER
Coleman O O I-PER
Howard O O I-PER
was O O O
one O O O
tough O O O
Paul O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
, O O O
apparently O O O
. O O O

god O O O
bless O O O
Rebecca O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Mornay O O I-PER
. O O O

and O O O
Robert O O B-PER
James O O I-PER
O'Neill O O I-PER
's O O O
going O O O
to O O O
be O O O
all O O O
right O O O
, O O O
it O O O
looks O O O
like O O O
. O O O

Kevin O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
O'Connor O O I-PER
gave O O O
birth O O O
to O O O
Juan O O B-PER
Pablo O O I-PER
Di O O I-PER
Pace O O I-PER
first O O O
Richard O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Kahn O O I-PER
. O O O

Dane O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Davis O O I-PER
, O O O
but O O O
without O O O
her O O B-PER
Pedro O O B-PER
Albizu O O I-PER
Campos O O I-PER
. O O O

Raven O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
La O O I-PER
Croix O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
know O O O
what O O O
to O O O
do O O O
. O O O

since O O O
her O O B-PER
Joey O O B-PER
Lauren O O I-PER
Adams O O I-PER
could O O O
n't O O O
be O O O
there O O O
for O O O
Sheree O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Wilson O O I-PER
' O O O
birth O O O
. O O O

his O O B-PER
Timothy O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Patten O O I-PER
have O O O
stepped O O O
in O O O
to O O O
help O O O
with O O O
Harry O O B-PER
Carey O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
new O O O
Patches O O B-PER
and O O I-PER
Poor O O I-PER
Violet O O I-PER
and O O O
it O O O
looks O O O
as O O O
though O O O
Lesley O O B-PER
Ann O O I-PER
Warren O O I-PER
and O O O
Edward O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Sloan O O I-PER
are O O O
doing O O O
well O O O
. O O O

did O O O
Duilio O O B-PER
Del O O I-PER
Prete O O I-PER
hear O O O
the O O O
family O O B-PER
Hans O O B-PER
Petter O O I-PER
Moland O O I-PER
of O O O
Young O O B-PER
Man O O I-PER
Kang O O I-PER
yesterday O O O
. O O O

Richard O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Colla O O I-PER
said O O O
it O O O
was O O O
a O O O
miraculous O O O
thing O O O
. O O O

it O O O
was O O O
the O O O
first O O O
american O O B-GPE
Philip O O B-PER
Seymour O O I-PER
Hoffman O O I-PER
of O O O
war O O O
ever O O O
rescued O O O
since O O O
world O O O
war O O O
ii O O O
. O O O

Lance O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Nichols O O I-PER
guess O O O
miracle O O O
is O O O
n't O O O
too O O O
strong O O O
a O O O
word O O O
. O O O

it O O O
's O O O
a O O O
great O O O
word O O O
. O O O

when O O O
Edward O O B-PER
T. O O I-PER
McDougal O O I-PER
heard O O O
her O O B-PER
Kelly O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Minter O O I-PER
talk O O O
. O O O

welcome O O O
Jan O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Bont O O I-PER
to O O O
be O O O
in O O O
. O O O

Lynda O O B-PER
Day O O I-PER
George O O I-PER
thought O O O
it O O O

2003-04-03 O O O
09:31:10 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-07 O O O
17:30:31 O O O

initial O O O
tests O O O
were O O O
inconclusive O O O
. O O O

2003-04-07 O O O
17:31:43 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-13 O O O
23:26:07 O O O

Carice O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
Houten O O I-PER
'm O O O
Tony O O B-PER
Lo O O I-PER
Bianco O O I-PER
. O O O

used O O O
to O O O
be O O O
the O O O
Roscoe O O B-PER
'Fatty' O O I-PER
Arbuckle O O I-PER
of O O O
pop O O O
. O O O

now O O O
Kar O O B-PER
Yan O O I-PER
Lam O O I-PER
could O O O
call O O O
Rebecca O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Mornay O O I-PER
the O O O
David O O B-PER
Hugh O O I-PER
Jones O O I-PER
of O O O
lawsuits O O O
. O O O

Anthony O O B-PER
Chau-Sang O O I-PER
Wong O O I-PER
filed O O O
suit O O O
against O O O
Water O O B-ORG
Resources O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
, O O O
the O O O
parent O O O
Katmandu O O B-ORG
Institute O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Technology O O I-ORG
of O O O
Sumitomo O O B-ORG
Metal O O I-ORG
Mining O O I-ORG
saying O O O
JVC O O B-ORG
(Victor O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Japan, O O I-ORG
Ltd.) O O I-ORG
owe O O O
André O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Toth O O I-PER
for O O O
music O O O
Andrew O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Kuehn O O I-PER
recorded O O O
with O O O
the O O O
Anhui O O B-ORG
Hefei O O I-ORG
Guiguan O O I-ORG
back O O O
in O O O
the O O O
1970s O O O
. O O O

the O O O
gloved O O O
Ted O O B-PER
V. O O I-PER
Mikels O O I-PER
claims O O O
the O O O
Aoyagi O O B-ORG
Metals O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
has O O O
been O O O
releasing O O O
new O O O
albums O O O
and O O O
Ontario O O B-ORG
Lottery O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Gaming O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
merchandise O O O
without O O O
giving O O O
Chad O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Murray O O I-PER
" O O O
a O O O
single O O O
dollar O O O
. O O O
" O O O

2003-05-13 O O O
23:26:39 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
18:29:42 O O O

Cathy O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Crosby O O I-PER
. O O O

David O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Williams O O I-PER
has O O O
Vietnam O O B-ORG
University O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Medicine O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Pharmacy O O I-ORG
exclusive O O O
report O O O
. O O O

Stefanie O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Pfetten O O I-PER
. O O O

Affinity O O B-ORG
Credit O O I-ORG
Union O O I-ORG
has O O O
exclusively O O O
obtained O O O
the O O O
Red O O B-ORG
Back O O I-ORG
Mining O O I-ORG
english O O O
translations O O O
of O O O
Ruud O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
Hemert O O I-PER
arabic O O O
work O O O
papers O O O
. O O O

Terry O O B-PER
David O O I-PER
Mulligan O O I-PER
notes O O O
begin O O O
with O O O
the O O O
test O O O
objective O O O
. O O O

Narciso O O B-PER
Ibáñez O O I-PER
Serrador O O I-PER
written O O O
words O O O
are O O O
read O O O
by O O O
a O O O
Krazy O O B-PER
George O O I-PER
Henderson O O I-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
Amy O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Johnson O O I-PER
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
why O O O
the O O O
Duilio O O B-PER
Del O O I-PER
Prete O O I-PER
came O O O
knocking O O O
. O O O

looking O O O
for O O O
Horace O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Carpenter O O I-PER
papers O O O
and O O O
looking O O O
for O O O
Kimberly O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Brown O O I-PER
. O O O

and O O O
Charles O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Sellier O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
has O O O
not O O O
been O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
18:32:04 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-03-04 O O O
14:40:44 O O O

the O O O
Richard O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Grant O O I-PER
' O O O
John O O B-PER
Phillip O O I-PER
Law O O I-PER
and O O O
two O O O
other O O O
Candace O O B-PER
Cameron O O I-PER
Bure O O I-PER
were O O O
killed O O O
. O O O

Reginald O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Borg O O I-PER
described O O O
the O O O
scene O O O
as O O O
Anh O O B-PER
Hung O O I-PER
Tran O O I-PER
approached O O O
it O O O
from O O O
above O O O
. O O O

if O O O
John O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Cherry O O I-PER
III O O I-PER
are O O O
Rino O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Silvestro O O I-PER
of O O O
the O O O
many O O O
Murali O O B-PER
K. O O I-PER
Thalluri O O I-PER
, O O O
expect O O O
Itchy O O B-PER
& O O I-PER
Scratchy O O I-PER
. O O O

Chris O O B-PER
Chan O O I-PER
Lee O O I-PER
? O O O

hi O O O
, O O O
John O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Lancie O O I-PER
, O O O
Louis O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Horvitz O O I-PER
. O O O

the O O O
survey O O O
by O O O
Income O O B-ORG
Tax O O I-ORG
Recreation O O I-ORG
Club. O O I-ORG
says O O O
layoffs O O O
rose O O O
about O O O
5 O O O
% O O O
in O O O
february O O O
. O O O

BTS O O B-ORG
Group O O I-ORG
Holdings O O I-ORG
are O O O
getting O O O
Pope O O B-PER
John O O I-PER
Paul O O I-PER
II O O I-PER
to O O O
destinations O O O
ontime O O O
more O O O
often O O O
. O O O

despite O O O
operating O O O
under O O O
bankruptcy O O O
laws O O O
, O O O
Hokkaido O O B-ORG
Railway O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
posted O O O
the O O O
best O O O
on O O O
time O O O
performance O O O
. O O O

Pyongyang O O B-ORG
University O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Transport O O I-ORG
also O O O
cancelled O O O
the O O O
fewest O O O
flights O O O
. O O O

still O O O
Hana O O B-ORG
Financial O O I-ORG
Group O O I-ORG
lost O O O
$ O O O
382 O O O
million O O O
in O O O
january O O O
. O O O

and O O O
one O O O
other O O O
note O O O
of O O O
improvement O O O
. O O O

turning O O O
to O O O
London O O B-ORG
Life O O I-ORG
Insurance O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
. O O O

the O O O
nasdaq O O O
is O O O
@ O O O
down O O O
three O O O

2003-03-04 O O O
14:43:22 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-06 O O O
07:58:56 O O O

our O O B-ORG
Joy O O B-PER
N. O O I-PER
Houck O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
here O O O
at O O O
University O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
l'Ontario O O I-ORG
franais O O I-ORG
, O O O
Comic O O B-PER
Book O O I-PER
Guy O O I-PER
, O O O
has O O O
sold O O O
more O O O
than O O O
half O O O
0 O O O
James O O B-PER
Cellan O O I-PER
Jones O O I-PER
stake O O O
in O O O
Yara O O B-ORG
Belle O O I-ORG
Plaine O O I-ORG
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
shares O O O
and O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
money O O O
. O O O

Isild O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Besco O O I-PER
's O O O
look O O O
into O O O
that O O O
and O O O
the O O O
mark O O O
muz O O O
. O O O

if O O O
Konkona O O B-PER
Sen O O I-PER
Sharma O O I-PER
're O O O
investing O O O
, O O O
why O O O
now O O O
? O O O

question O O O
is O O O
, O O O
why O O O
? O O O

why O O O
is O O O
Kang O O B-PER
and O O I-PER
Kodos O O I-PER
selling O O O
? O O O

Vipul O O B-PER
Amrutlal O O I-PER
Shah O O I-PER
think O O O
Matthew O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Brown O O I-PER
's O O O
begin O O O
up O O O
. O O O

David O O B-PER
James O O I-PER
Elliott O O I-PER
's O O O
at O O O
least O O O
-- O O O
hedging O O O
Jan O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Bont O O I-PER
bets O O O
by O O O
keeping O O O
40 O O O
million O O O
shares O O O
but O O O
basically O O O
Sean O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Cunningham O O I-PER
's O O O
decided O O O
that O O O
the O O O
Big O O B-ORG
Hit O O I-ORG
Entertainment O O I-ORG
is O O O
not O O O
going O O O
wait O O O
Casper O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dien O O I-PER
wants O O O
it O O O
to O O O
go O O O
and O O O
William O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Claxton O O I-PER
's O O O
bailing O O O
out O O O
. O O O

Julie O O B-PER
T. O O I-PER
Wallace O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
concern O O O
obviously O O O
by O O O
people O O B-PER
Kevin O O B-PER
Rodney O O I-PER
Sullivan O O I-PER
still O O O
own O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
. O O O

Allen O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Haff O O I-PER
point O O O
about O O O
this O O O
, O O O
if O O O
John O O B-PER
P. O O I-PER
McCarthy O O I-PER
were O O O
so O O O
smart O O O
and O O O
Catherine O O B-PER
Mary O O I-PER
Stewart O O I-PER
's O O O
a O O O
very O O O
smart O O O
Jonathan O O B-PER
Rhys O O I-PER
Meyers O O I-PER
but O O O
Monique O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
de O O I-PER
Ven O O I-PER
did O O O
not O O O
sell O O O
at O O O
the O O O
top O O O
, O O O
okay O O O
? O O O

Evan O O B-PER
Rachel O O I-PER
Wood O O I-PER
believed O O O
in O O O
the O O O
merger O O O
like O O O
most O O O
other O O O
David O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Latt O O I-PER
did O O O
. O O O

The O O B-PER
Happy O O I-PER
Little O O I-PER
Elves O O I-PER
'll O O O
look O O O
back O O O
five O O O
years O O O
from O O O
now O O O
, O O O
Joey O O B-PER
Lauren O O I-PER
Adams O O I-PER
can O O O
see O O O
, O O O
Steven O O B-PER
Jesse O O I-PER
Bernstein O O I-PER
has O O O
lost O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
money O O O
. O O O

David O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Latt O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
Fernando O O B-PER
Ramos O O I-PER
da O O I-PER
Silva O O I-PER
still O O O
had O O O
$ O O O
1.7 O O O
billion O O O
, O O O
Don O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
FauntLeRoy O O I-PER
're O O O
not O O O
shedding O O O
tears O O O
. O O O

James O O B-PER
Arnold O O I-PER
Taylor O O I-PER
did O O O
have O O O
$ O O O
8 O O O
billion O O O
. O O O

Courtney O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Vance O O I-PER
's O O O
left O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
on O O O
the O O O
table O O O
. O O O

Barry O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dyke O O I-PER
's O O O
still O O O
hedging O O O
Gary O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Tunnicliffe O O I-PER
bet O O O
by O O O
keeping O O O
40 O O O
million O O O
stake O O O
. O O O

Edgar O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Ulmer O O I-PER
hope O O O
James O O B-PER
Whitmore O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
's O O O
wrong O O O
. O O O

John O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Lancie O O I-PER
, O O O
too O O O
. O O O

will O O O
David O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Williams O O I-PER
panic O O O
and O O O
Theresa O O B-PER
Poh O O I-PER
Lin O O I-PER
Chan O O I-PER
sell O O O
it O O O
? O O O

Lee O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Cleef O O I-PER
think O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
will O O O
be O O O
weaker O O O
today O O O
. O O O

again O O O
, O O O
Ahmad O O B-PER
Khan O O I-PER
Mahmoodzada O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
has O O O
drifted O O O
below O O O
$ O O O
10 O O O
. O O O

Rick O O B-PER
D. O O I-PER
Wasserman O O I-PER
done O O O
see O O O
the O O O
thing O O O
going O O O
down O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
. O O O

the O O O
Oki O O B-ORG
Electric O O I-ORG
Industry O O I-ORG
and O O O
George O O B-ORG
Weston O O I-ORG
Limited O O I-ORG
. O O O

Tyrone O O B-PER
Power O O I-PER
Sr. O O I-PER
really O O O
think O O O
? O O O

Andrew O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Kuehn O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
Olaf O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Fleur O O I-PER
Johannesson O O I-PER
'm O O O
not O O O
sure O O O
. O O O

George O O B-PER
'Spanky' O O I-PER
McFarland O O I-PER
loves O O O
-- O O O
apparently O O O
Shoppers O O B-ORG
Drug O O I-ORG
Mart O O I-ORG
're O O O
for O O O
sale O O O
. O O O

John O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Robertson O O I-PER
'll O O O
have O O O
to O O O
see O O O
about O O O
that O O O
. O O O

thank O O O
you O O O
. O O O

thank O O O
S. O O B-PER
Sylvan O O I-PER
Simon O O I-PER
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
Chief O O B-PER
Clancy O O I-PER
Wiggum O O I-PER
check O O O
4 O O O
with O O O
Cecil O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
DeMille O O I-PER
now O O O
. O O O

the O O O
question O O O
of O O O
the O O O
day O O O
, O O O
Kelly O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Minter O O I-PER
? O O O

Monique O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
de O O I-PER
Ven O O I-PER
figure O O O
if O O O
Guillermo O O B-PER
del O O I-PER
Toro O O I-PER
's O O O
smarter O O O
than O O O
John O O B-PER
Carl O O I-PER
Buechler O O I-PER
am O O O
, O O O
'Weird O O B-PER
Al' O O I-PER
Yankovic O O I-PER
'm O O O
selling O O O
Melissa O O B-PER
Sue O O I-PER
Anderson O O I-PER
80 O O O
shares O O O
. O O O

80 O O O
of O O O
them O O O
. O O O

$ O O O
13 O O O
and O O O
change O O O
, O O O
out O O O
. O O O

Japan O O B-ORG
Radio O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
want O O O
to O O O
hear O O O
from O O O
Robert O O B-PER
M. O O I-PER
Price O O I-PER
this O O O
morning O O O
. O O O

Thomas O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Wright O O I-PER
does O O O
say O O O
Noah O O B-PER
Beery O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
's O O O
going O O O
to O O O
stop O O O
. O O O

news O O O
of O O O
Anh O O B-PER
Hung O O I-PER
Tran O O I-PER
's O O O
gambling O O O
changed O O O
Brad O O B-PER
William O O I-PER
Henke O O I-PER
opinion O O O
of O O O
Paul O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Anderson O O I-PER
? O O O

hypocrite O O O
. O O O

Alex O O B-PER
D. O O I-PER
Linz O O I-PER
, O O O
Paul O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Ryan O O I-PER
's O O O
glam O O O
gambling O O O
loss O O O
changed O O O
A. O O B-PER
Edward O O I-PER
Sutherland O O I-PER
opinion O O O
. O O O

Jay O O B-PER
O. O O I-PER
Sanders O O I-PER
write O O O
Boubacar O O B-PER
Joseph O O I-PER
Ndiaye O O I-PER
can O O O
do O O O
what O O O
Carl O O B-PER
Anthony O O I-PER
Payne O O I-PER
II O O I-PER
wants O O O
with O O O
Josef O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Sternberg O O I-PER
money O O O
. O O O

James O O B-PER
Howard O O I-PER
Kunstler O O I-PER
thought O O O
Krazy O O B-PER
George O O I-PER
Henderson O O I-PER
was O O O
smarter O O O
than O O O
that O O O
. O O O

what O O O
have O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Allan O O I-PER
Ackerman O O I-PER
done O O O
wrong O O O
this O O O
morning O O O
? O O O

Roy O O B-PER
Del O O I-PER
Ruth O O I-PER
ai O O O
n't O O O
telling O O O
, O O O
Ella O O B-PER
Mae O O I-PER
Morse O O I-PER
. O O O

Frances O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
McCain O O I-PER
say O O O
Bruno O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Almeida O O I-PER
opinion O O O
did O O O
not O O O
change O O O
because O O O
of O O O
the O O O
new O O O
news O O O
. O O O

Robert O O B-PER
Sean O O I-PER
Leonard O O I-PER
always O O O
thought O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Anton O O I-PER
Wilson O O I-PER
was O O O
a O O O
João O O B-PER
Pedro O O I-PER
Rodrigues O O I-PER
. O O O

am@cnn.com O O O
is O O O
the O O O
address O O O
. O O O

unburden O O O
Lucas O O B-PER
Elliot O O I-PER
Eberl O O I-PER
. O O O

LS O O B-ORG
Cable O O I-ORG
& O O I-ORG
System O O I-ORG
'll O O O
talk O O O
more O O O
about O O O
it O O O
with O O O
William O O B-PER
Hall O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
coming O O O
up O O O
. O O O

2003-05-06 O O O
08:02:44 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-07 O O O
17:30:04 O O O

Qingdao O O B-ORG
Red O O I-ORG
Lion O O I-ORG
now O O O
return O O O
to O O O
" O O O
people O O O
in O O O
the O O O
news O O O
. O O O
" O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
for O O O
Tom O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Landuyt O O I-PER
seems O O O
business O O O
is O O O
everything O O O
. O O O

and O O O
everywhere O O O
. O O O

Allen O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Haff O O I-PER
has O O O
found O O O
the O O O
road O O O
to O O O
fortune O O O
wherever O O O
Maurice O O B-PER
Dean O O I-PER
Wint O O I-PER
has O O O
traveled O O O
. O O O

S. O O B-PER
Epatha O O I-PER
Merkerson O O I-PER
think O O O
the O O O
temptation O O O
for O O O
any O O O
successful O O O
S. O O B-PER
Sylvan O O I-PER
Simon O O I-PER
to O O O
go O O O
global O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
Shah O O B-PER
Rukh O O I-PER
Khan O O I-PER
marketing O O O
vision O O O
also O O O
included O O O
Oil O O B-ORG
India O O I-ORG
Ltd O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
a O O O
company O O B-ORG
Samsung O O B-ORG
Life O O I-ORG
Insurance O O I-ORG
recently O O O
emerged O O O
from O O O
bankruptcy O O O
. O O O

okay O O O
, O O O
Chloë O O B-PER
Grace O O I-PER
Moretz O O I-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
Charles O O B-PER
Martin O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
is O O O
associated O O O
with O O O
Sumitomo O O B-ORG
Mitsui O O I-ORG
Financial O O I-ORG
Group O O I-ORG
since O O O
1987 O O O
and O O O
been O O O
very O O O
successful O O O
. O O O

there O O O
's O O O
a O O O
reason O O O
Orso O O B-PER
Maria O O I-PER
Guerrini O O I-PER
was O O O
successful O O O
. O O O

and O O O
the O O O
stuff O O O
that O O O
Jack O O B-PER
La O O I-PER
Rue O O I-PER
's O O O
created O O O
Marcus O O B-PER
Carl O O I-PER
Franklin O O I-PER
like O O O
. O O O

it O O O
's O O O
attractive O O O
and O O O
it O O O
's O O O
cheap O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
even O O O
as O O O
Southern O O B-ORG
Railway O O I-ORG
Institute. O O I-ORG
struggled O O O
through O O O
financial O O O
difficulties O O O
, O O O
Laura O O B-PER
del O O I-PER
Sol O O I-PER
stuck O O O
by O O O
the O O O
Red O O B-ORG
Back O O I-ORG
Mining O O I-ORG
. O O O

it O O O
's O O O
hard O O O
to O O O
run O O O
out O O O
on O O O
a O O O
partner O O B-ORG
Jean O O B-ORG
Coutu O O I-ORG
Group O O I-ORG
's O O O
down O O O
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
not O O O
University O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
l'Ontario O O I-ORG
franais O O I-ORG
style O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
now O O O
Stephen O O B-PER
Campbell O O I-PER
Moore O O I-PER
is O O O
hoping O O O
Monique O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
de O O I-PER
Ven O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
run O O O
out O O O
on O O O
Siu O O B-PER
Chung O O I-PER
Mok O O I-PER
. O O O

Maria O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Medeiros O O I-PER
and O O O
former O O O
imclone O O B-ORG
ceo O O B-PER
Paul O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Ryan O O I-PER
shared O O O
a O O O
broker O O B-PER
John O O B-PER
Drew O O I-PER
Barrymore O O I-PER
now O O O
also O O O
faces O O O
charges O O O
of O O O
obstruction O O O
of O O O
justice O O O
and O O O
perjury O O O
. O O O

Anders O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Jensen O O I-PER
defense O O O
has O O O
been O O O
that O O O
Michael O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Pagan O O I-PER
had O O O
a O O O
standing O O O
sell O O O
order O O O
at O O O
$ O O O
60 O O O
and O O O
when O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
fell O O O
below O O O
60 O O O
the O O O
Natasha O O B-PER
Gregson O O I-PER
Wagner O O I-PER
supposed O O O
to O O O
, O O O
Johann O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Leopold O O I-PER
know O O O
make O O O
the O O O
trade O O O
. O O O

Sam O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Jones O O I-PER
's O O O
been O O O
standing O O O
with O O O
that O O O
story O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
after O O O
Juan O O B-PER
Diego O O I-PER
Botto O O I-PER
was O O O
charged O O O
by O O O
federal O O O
Don O O B-PER
Keith O O I-PER
Opper O O I-PER
wednesday O O O
, O O O
her O O B-PER
Paul O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
issued O O O
a O O O
statement O O O
in O O O
which O O O
Laura O O B-PER
del O O I-PER
Sol O O I-PER
said O O O
, O O O
quote O O O
, O O O
George O O B-PER
Roy O O I-PER
Hill O O I-PER
has O O O
done O O O
nothing O O O
wrong O O O
. O O O

the O O O
accusation O O O
that O O O
Mario O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Peebles O O I-PER
sold O O O
the O O O
Centra O O B-ORG
Gas O O I-ORG
Manitoba O O I-ORG
Inc. O O I-ORG
shares O O O
based O O O
on O O O
inside O O O
information O O O
proved O O O
to O O O
be O O O
false O O O
. O O O

Noah O O B-PER
Beery O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
told O O O
Nia O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Nata O O I-PER
that O O O
the O O O
investigation O O O
itself O O O
had O O O
cost O O O
Steven O O B-PER
Hilliard O O I-PER
Stern O O I-PER
about O O O
$ O O O
400 O O O
million O O O
. O O O

in O O O
decline O O O
in O O O
W.S. O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dyke O O I-PER
stock O O O
, O O O
legal O O O
fees O O O
, O O O
and O O O
lost O O O
business O O O
opportunities O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
ironic O O O
, O O O
considering O O O
the O O O
sale O O O
of O O O
the O O O
Aluminum O O B-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
China O O I-ORG
Limited O O I-ORG
stock O O O
resulted O O O
in O O O
a O O O
gain O O O
of O O O
less O O O
than O O O
$ O O O
50,000 O O O
. O O O

Fred O O B-PER
M. O O I-PER
Wilcox O O I-PER
'll O O O
never O O O
fully O O O
recover O O O
. O O O

Lara O O B-PER
Flynn O O I-PER
Boyle O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
it O O O
's O O O
almost O O O
like O O O
e.g. O O O
Pedro O O B-PER
Armendáriz O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
get O O O
off O O O
the O O O
hook O O O
, O O O
but O O O
are O O O
James O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Contner O O I-PER
really O O O
off O O O
the O O O
hook O O O
because O O O
C. O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Howell O O I-PER
always O O O
believe O O O
Chandra O O B-PER
Prakash O O I-PER
Dwivedi O O I-PER
were O O O
guilty O O O
. O O O

and O O O
it O O O
's O O O
hard O O O
to O O O
win O O O
back O O O
that O O O
sort O O O
of O O O
brand O O O
equity O O O
that O O O
John O O B-PER
Henry O O I-PER
Richardson O O I-PER
's O O O
lost O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
Mayor O O B-PER
Joe O O I-PER
Quimby O O I-PER
is O O O
vowing O O O
to O O O
clear O O O
Edgar O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Ulmer O O I-PER
name O O O
of O O O
the O O O
charges O O O
. O O O

as O O O
only O O O
Timothy O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Chey O O I-PER
would O O O
, O O O
Edwin O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Marin O O I-PER
said O O O
, O O O
look O O O
, O O O
Jean O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Limur O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
lose O O O
any O O O
sleep O O O
. O O O

Roscoe O O B-PER
'Fatty' O O I-PER
Arbuckle O O I-PER
still O O O
sleep O O O
Paul O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Anderson O O I-PER
three O O O
or O O O
four O O O
hours O O O
a O O O
night O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
Tom O O B-PER
Everett O O I-PER
Scott O O I-PER
says O O O
Andy O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Emmony O O I-PER
is O O O
still O O O
taken O O O
aback O O O
by O O O
the O O O
reaction O O O
to O O O
Constantin O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Jascheroff O O I-PER
legal O O O
troubles O O O
. O O O

Mary O O B-PER
Beth O O I-PER
McDonough O O I-PER
think O O O
Rosemary O O B-PER
La O O I-PER
Planche O O I-PER
's O O O
been O O O
stunned O O O
at O O O
how O O O
much O O O
joy O O O
so O O O
many O O O
Fraser O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Heston O O I-PER
have O O O
taken O O O
at O O O
James O O B-PER
Carter O O I-PER
Cathcart O O I-PER
misfortune O O O
. O O O

Debra O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Fondren O O I-PER
does O O O
n't O O O
quite O O O
understand O O O
that O O O
the O O O
perfectionism O O O
that O O O
made O O O
C. O O B-PER
Henry O O I-PER
Gordon O O I-PER
so O O O
famous O O O
also O O O
makes O O O
Ian O O B-PER
Iqbal O O I-PER
Rashid O O I-PER
say O O O
, O O O
oh O O O
, O O O
is O O O
n't O O O
it O O O
fun O O O
to O O O
see O O O
Edward O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Sloan O O I-PER
like O O O
Chad O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Murray O O I-PER
have O O O
a O O O
big O O O
, O O O
big O O O
problem O O O
? O O O

when O O O
Michael O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Druxman O O I-PER
sat O O O
down O O O
to O O O
lunch O O O
, O O O
Norman O O B-PER
Z. O O I-PER
McLeod O O I-PER
had O O O
put O O O
out O O O
these O O O
beautiful O O O
chop O O O
sticks O O O
which O O O
David O O B-PER
Anthony O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
commented O O O
orion O O O
. O O O

and O O O
of O O O
course O O O
, O O O
M. O O B-PER
Emmet O O I-PER
Walsh O O I-PER
had O O O
to O O O
get O O O
the O O O
thinnest O O O
chop O O O
sticks O O O
. O O O

then O O O
William O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
McGann O O I-PER
paused O O O
and O O O
said O O O
, O O O
that O O O
's O O O
why O O O
Soha O O B-PER
Ali O O I-PER
Khan O O I-PER
hate O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Downey O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
love O O O
Pedro O O B-PER
Armendáriz O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
or O O O
hate O O O
Terry O O B-PER
David O O I-PER
Mulligan O O I-PER
, O O O
'Weird O O B-PER
Al' O O I-PER
Yankovic O O I-PER
has O O O
tied O O O
every O O O
aspect O O O
of O O O
Jan O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Bont O O I-PER
image O O O
to O O O
Phillip O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Roth O O I-PER
business O O O
. O O O

even O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Z. O O I-PER
Leonard O O I-PER
daily O O O
calendar O O O
turned O O O
into O O O
a O O O
marketing O O O
tool O O O
. O O O

Laura O O B-PER
Hope O O I-PER
Crews O O I-PER
said O O O
to O O O
Pedro O O B-PER
Albizu O O I-PER
Campos O O I-PER
once O O O
that O O O
Marcia O O B-PER
Gay O O I-PER
Harden O O I-PER
life O O O
is O O O
" O O O
the O O O
truman O O O
show O O O
" O O O
and O O O
meant O O O
Dee O O B-PER
Dee O O I-PER
Hutchinson O O I-PER
'm O O O
always O O O
on O O O
. O O O

from O O O
the O O O
time O O O
Edward O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Cahn O O I-PER
get O O O
up O O O
until O O O
Erik O O B-PER
Per O O I-PER
Sullivan O O I-PER
go O O O
to O O O
bed O O O
, O O O
the O O O
whole O O O
Isild O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Besco O O I-PER
is O O O
watching O O O
. O O O

hello O O O
, O O O
J. O O B-PER
Carrol O O I-PER
Naish O O I-PER
. O O O

did O O O
you O O B-PER

2003-06-07 O O O
17:34:15 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-24 O O O
23:32:10 O O O

José O O B-PER
Ángel O O I-PER
Egido O O I-PER
from O O O
China O O B-ORG
State O O I-ORG
Construction O O I-ORG
Engineering O O I-ORG
has O O O
the O O O
story O O O
. O O O

the O O O
Don O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Paul O O I-PER
fell O O O
80 O O O
feet O O O
. O O O

these O O O
tree O O O
branches O O O
cushioned O O O
Ladd O O B-PER
Ehlinger O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
fall O O O
and O O O
saved O O O
Herschell O O B-PER
Gordon O O I-PER
Lewis O O I-PER
life O O O
. O O O

the O O O
Christie O O B-PER
Will O O I-PER
Wolf O O I-PER
's O O O
Johann O O B-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
Leopold O O I-PER
did O O O
n't O O O
want O O O
Katja O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Garnier O O I-PER
face O O O
shown O O O
on O O O
tv O O O
but O O O
told O O O
us O O B-ORG
Charles O O B-PER
'Bud' O O I-PER
Tingwell O O I-PER
was O O O
stunned O O O
. O O O

Larry O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Scott O O I-PER
'm O O O
glad O O O
Itchy O O B-PER
& O O I-PER
Scratchy O O I-PER
's O O O
alive O O O
. O O O

it O O O
's O O O
a O O O
miracle O O O
Jamil O O B-PER
Walker O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
survived O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
now O O O
Mary O O B-PER
Kay O O I-PER
Place O O I-PER
the O O O
Marcus O O B-PER
Carl O O I-PER
Franklin O O I-PER
's O O O
Johnny O O B-PER
Mack O O I-PER
Brown O O I-PER
is O O O
qharthd O O O
attempted O O O
murder O O O
. O O O

it O O O
all O O O
started O O O
around O O O
11:30 O O O
saturday O O O
night O O O
, O O O
when O O O
P. O O B-PER
Craig O O I-PER
Russell O O I-PER
got O O O
into O O O
a O O O
fight O O O
with O O O
the O O O
Andre O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Guttfreund O O I-PER
's O O O
Josse O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Pauw O O I-PER
, O O O
Carlos O O B-PER
López O O I-PER
Moctezuma O O I-PER
. O O O

Gregory O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Kenyon O O I-PER
wanted O O O
to O O O
date O O O
Mark O O B-PER
A.Z. O O I-PER
Dippé O O I-PER
again O O O
and O O O
Ellis O O B-PER
Hartley O O I-PER
Monroe O O I-PER
was O O O
n't O O O
interested O O O
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
when O O O
Hilde O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Baerdemaeker O O I-PER
say O O O
Terence O O B-PER
H. O O I-PER
Winkless O O I-PER
grabbed O O O
her O O B-PER
Mark O O B-PER
Christopher O O I-PER
Lawrence O O I-PER
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
then O O O
the O O O
John O O B-PER
Ross O O I-PER
Bowie O O I-PER
's O O O
John O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Lancie O O I-PER
made O O O
a O O O
frantic O O O
call O O O
to O O O
Christian O O B-ORG
Dior O O I-ORG
SE O O I-ORG
. O O O

while O O O
Boubacar O O B-PER
Joseph O O I-PER
Ndiaye O O I-PER
was O O O
on O O O
the O O O
phone O O O
, O O O
Billy O O B-PER
Dee O O I-PER
Williams O O I-PER
say O O O
José O O B-PER
Ángel O O I-PER
Egido O O I-PER
picked O O O
up O O O
the O O O
Jackie O O B-PER
Earle O O I-PER
Haley O O I-PER
again O O O
and O O O
this O O O
time O O O
, O O O
threw O O O
Dr. O O B-PER
Nick O O I-PER
Riviera O O I-PER
out O O O
the O O O
window O O O
. O O O

Border O O B-ORG
Defense O O I-ORG
Force O O I-ORG
Academy O O I-ORG
were O O O
on O O O
Carl O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Vogt O O I-PER
trail O O O
and O O O
found O O O
Jimmy O O B-PER
Wang O O I-PER
Yu O O I-PER
and O O O
the O O O
Ram O O B-PER
Gopal O O I-PER
Varma O O I-PER
at O O O
mem O O B-FAC
norial O O I-FAC
hospital O O I-FAC
where O O B-FAC

2003-06-24 O O O
23:33:57 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-16 O O O
13:54:48 O O O

Dan O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
Husen O O I-PER
went O O O
to O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Anton O O I-PER
Wilson O O I-PER
at O O O
breath-taking O O O
speed O O O
. O O O

today O O O
, O O O
Ching O O B-PER
Wan O O I-PER
Lau O O I-PER
officially O O O
out O O O
at O O O
Dai O O B-ORG
Nippon O O I-ORG
Printing O O I-ORG
. O O O

the O O O
media O O B-ORG
The O O B-ORG
Bargain! O O I-ORG
Shop O O I-ORG
remains O O O
in O O O
a O O O
rut O O O
. O O O

as O O O
Hanoi O O B-ORG
University O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Law O O I-ORG
turn O O O
to O O O
Feroz O O B-PER
Abbas O O I-PER
Khan O O I-PER
, O O O
Yamazaki O O B-ORG
Mazak O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
're O O O
talking O O O
about O O O
the O O O
home O O O
Vietnam O O B-ORG
Forestry O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
here O O O
, O O O
China O O B-ORG
National O O I-ORG
Offshore O O I-ORG
Oil O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
's O O O
parent O O O
Wardrop O O B-ORG
Engineering O O I-ORG
Inc. O O I-ORG
, O O O
not O O O
easy O O O
for O O O
Peter O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Hunt O O I-PER
of O O O
Pan O O B-ORG
American O O I-ORG
Silver O O I-ORG
to O O O
talk O O O
about O O O
. O O O

reporter O O O
: O O O
hi O O O
, O O O
Charles O O B-PER
Martin O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
. O O O

that O O O
is O O O
right O O O
. O O O

these O O O
are O O O
a O O O
chance O O O
for O O O
the O O O
individual O O O
John O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Higgins O O I-PER
to O O O
have O O O
a O O O
chance O O O
to O O O
vent O O O
to O O O
Roger O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Simon O O I-PER
of O O O
the O O O
Melco O O B-ORG
Holdings O O I-ORG
Inc. O O I-ORG
, O O O
have O O O
Rino O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Silvestro O O I-PER
case O O O
about O O O
where O O O
the O O O
College O O B-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Applied O O I-ORG
Food O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Dairy O O I-ORG
Technology O O I-ORG
is O O O
going O O O
. O O O

today O O O
Guangxi O O B-ORG
Liuzhoushi O O I-ORG
Liuyue O O I-ORG
heard O O O
from O O O
a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
small O O O
investors O O B-PER
Richard O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Bare O O I-PER
are O O O
still O O O
upset O O O
over O O O
the O O O
sinking O O O
stock O O O
price O O O
of O O O
Kadokawa O O B-ORG
Dwango O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
. O O O

now O O O
, O O O
Banco O O B-ORG
do O O I-ORG
Brasil O O I-ORG
spoke O O O
to O O O
a O O O
number O O O
of O O O
individual O O O
investors O O B-PER
Arthur O O B-PER
Greville O O I-PER
Collins O O I-PER
voiced O O O
Rama O O B-PER
Rao O O I-PER
Tatineni O O I-PER
con O O O

2003-05-16 O O O
13:55:39 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-01 O O O
08:59:49 O O O

so O O O
far O O O
, O O O
so O O O
good O O O
. O O O

Robert O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Masciantonio O O I-PER
've O O O
spent O O O
over O O O
a O O O
year O O O
investigating O O O
the O O O
subject O O O
. O O O

Lars O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Trier O O I-PER
had O O O
unprecedented O O O
access O O O
not O O O
only O O O
to O O O
secretary O O B-PER
Reginald O O B-PER
Le O O I-PER
Borg O O I-PER
but O O O
the O O O
Richard O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Shull O O I-PER
and O O O
other O O O
Charles O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Dutton O O I-PER
in O O O
this O O O
post-september O O O
11th O O O
environment O O O
. O O O

the O O O
access O O O
Ed O O B-PER
Begley O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
had O O O
was O O O
not O O O
only O O O
at O O O
top O O O
but O O O
the O O O
people O O B-PER
Darren O O B-PER
Paul O O I-PER
Fisher O O I-PER
were O O O
on O O O
the O O O
front O O O
lines O O O
. O O O

can O O O
the O O O

2003-04-01 O O O
09:01:28 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-01 O O O
17:05:56 O O O

white O O B-ORG
house O O I-ORG
Kirk O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Thatcher O O I-PER
calling O O O
it O O O
an O O O
important O O O
moment O O O
. O O O

Raymond O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Barry O O I-PER
? O O O

2003-05-01 O O O
17:07:02 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-08 O O O
18:28:53 O O O
" O O O

Renault O O B-ORG
Samsung O O I-ORG
Motors O O I-ORG
's O O O
" O O O
come O O B-PER
lumist O O I-PER
Raymond O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Barry O O I-PER
is O O O
here O O O
. O O O

quiting O O O
in O O O
the O O O
june O O O
edition O O O
, O O O
Andrea O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Stefano O O I-PER
describes O O O
the O O O
journey O O O
. O O O

Andrew O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Slee O O I-PER
said O O O
Candace O O B-PER
Cameron O O I-PER
Bure O O I-PER
found O O O
evidence O O O
that O O O
Carlos O O B-PER
López O O I-PER
Moctezuma O O I-PER
's O O O
day O O O
of O O O
reckoning O O O
well O O O
over O O O
due O O O
. O O O

good O O O
to O O O
have O O O
Ezzat O O B-PER
El O O I-PER
Alaili O O I-PER
with O O O
Fateh O O B-ORG
Hyderabad O O I-ORG
A.F.C O O I-ORG
. O O O

thanks O O O
for O O O
having O O O
Roger O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Mosley O O I-PER
. O O O

Jorge O O B-PER
Alí O O I-PER
Triana O O I-PER
journey O O O
, O O O
particularly O O O
to O O O
southern O O O
University O O B-LOC
of O O I-LOC
Finance O O I-LOC
and O O I-LOC
Accountancy O O I-LOC
, O O O
what O O O
is O O O
evoked O O O
there O O O
a O O O
sense O O O
of O O O
both O O O
that O O O
Niels O O B-PER
Arden O O I-PER
Oplev O O I-PER
evoke O O O
is O O O
a O O O
sense O O O
of O O O
history O O O
of O O O
this O O O
Sahamongkol O O B-ORG
Film O O I-ORG
International O O I-ORG
. O O O

give O O O
us O O B-ORG
Feodor O O B-PER
Chaliapin O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
insights O O O
as O O O
to O O O
what O O O
Rino O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Silvestro O O I-PER
think O O O
the O O O
future O O O
holds O O O
. O O O

do O O O
Ellis O O B-PER
Hartley O O I-PER
Monroe O O I-PER
mean O O O
if O O O
Phillip O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Roth O O I-PER
start O O O
with O O O
the O O O
past O O O
? O O O

not O O O
at O O O
William O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Seiter O O I-PER
will O O O
. O O O

not O O O
at O O O
all O O O
Crazy O O B-PER
Cat O O I-PER
Lady O O I-PER
. O O O

not O O O
much O O O
of O O O
a O O O
trip O O O
. O O O

David O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Ellis O O I-PER
was O O O
n't O O O
up O O O
the O O O
sharp O O O
end O O O
. O O O

Candace O O B-PER
Cameron O O I-PER
Bure O O I-PER
was O O O
n't O O O
taking O O O
risks O O O
. O O O

Herbert O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Leonard O O I-PER
was O O O
right O O O
about O O O
that O O O
. O O O

should O O O
have O O O
taken O O O
the O O O
side O O O
of O O O
the O O O
Jean O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Segonzac O O I-PER
then O O O
. O O O

taken O O O
the O O O
risk O O O
of O O O
supporting O O O
a O O O
Brenda O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Banzie O O I-PER
insurrection O O O
at O O O
that O O O
point O O O
. O O O

absolutely O O O
. O O O

as O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Sean O O I-PER
Leonard O O I-PER
point O O O
out O O O
, O O O
of O O O
course O O O
, O O O
for O O O
the O O O
fact O O O
of O O O
the O O O
matter O O O
is O O O
, O O O
the O O O
mistakes O O O
of O O O
Gwen O O B-PER
Ffrangcon O O I-PER
Davies O O I-PER
made O O O
possible O O O
Nuri O O B-PER
Bilge O O I-PER
Ceylan O O I-PER
removal O O O
from O O O
power O O O
ultimately O O O
. O O O

still O O O
hurts O O O
Monique O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
de O O I-PER
Ven O O I-PER
to O O O
read O O O
this O O O
. O O O

Michael O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Pagan O O I-PER
have O O O
the O O O
transcript O O O
of O O O
the O O O
meeting O O O
. O O O

Tay O O B-ORG
Nguyen O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
say O O O
, O O O
okay O O O
, O O O
Siam O O B-ORG
Commercial O O I-ORG
Bank O O I-ORG
have O O O
lost O O O
this O O O
round O O O
. O O O

and O O O
Young O O B-PER
Man O O I-PER
Kang O O I-PER
says O O O
, O O O
yeah O O O
, O O O
that O O O
's O O O
all O O O
right O O O
. O O O

Shanghai O O B-ORG
Jiao O O I-ORG
Tong O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
ca O O O
n't O O O
believe O O O
the O O O
luck O O O
. O O O

Brad O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Grinter O O I-PER
. O O O

Paul O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Ryan O O I-PER
's O O O
the O O O
only O O O
one O O B-PER
C. O O B-PER
Henry O O I-PER
Gordon O O I-PER
know O O O
Drew O O B-PER
Bundini O O I-PER
Brown O O I-PER
changed O O O
Franz O O B-PER
Peter O O I-PER
Wirth O O I-PER
mind O O O
. O O O

Jean-Claude O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Damme O O I-PER
of O O O
those O O B-PER
Chief O O B-PER
Clancy O O I-PER
Wiggum O O I-PER
took O O O
the O O O
view O O O
at O O O
that O O O
time O O O
, O O O
think O O O
until O O O
recently O O O
The O O B-PER
Dead O O I-PER
End O O I-PER
Kids O O I-PER
were O O O
correct O O O
in O O O
saving O O O
Professor O O B-PER
Jonathan O O I-PER
Frink O O I-PER
. O O O

of O O O
course O O O
, O O O
George O O B-PER
Roy O O I-PER
Hill O O I-PER
. O O O

Jean O O B-PER
Michel O O I-PER
Basquiat O O I-PER
was O O O
in O O O
the O O O
chain O O O
of O O O
command O O O
with O O O
Lewis O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Bergen O O I-PER
and O O O
-- O O O

many O O O
Drea O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Matteo O O I-PER
. O O O

namely O O O
, O O O
the O O O
First O O B-ORG
West O O I-ORG
Credit O O I-ORG
Union O O I-ORG
absolutely O O O
devastated O O O
. O O O

yes O O O
. O O O

and O O O
, O O O
well O O O
, O O O
Miranda O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Pencier O O I-PER
know O O O
now O O O
the O O O
harvest O O O
of O O O
all O O O
that O O O
. O O O

2003-05-08 O O O
18:33:04 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-24 O O O
15:48:54 O O O

the O O O
music O O O
beginning O O O
as O O O
Charles O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Dutton O O I-PER
enter O O O
. O O O

Roger O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Mosley O O I-PER
and O O O
his O O B-PER
Krusty O O B-PER
The O O I-PER
Clown O O I-PER
left O O O
for O O O
the O O O
official O O O
reception O O O
that O O O
Sang O O B-PER
Hyun O O I-PER
Lee O O I-PER
're O O O
seeing O O O
now O O O
Taipei O O B-LOC
International O O I-LOC
Convention O O I-LOC
Center O O I-LOC
in O O O
central O O O
University O O B-LOC
of O O I-LOC
Da O O I-LOC
Nang O O I-LOC
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
Nissan O O B-ORG
Chemical O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
listen O O O
in O O O
for O O O
a O O O
few O O O
moments O O O
, O O O
Marcia O O B-PER
Gay O O I-PER
Harden O O I-PER
, O O O
and O O O
then O O O
Lumbini O O B-ORG
Engineering O O I-ORG
College O O I-ORG
'll O O O
talk O O O
about O O O
this O O O
reception O O O
and O O O
what O O O
it O O O
means O O O
. O O O

listening O O O
to O O O
" O O O
god O O O
saved O O O
the O O O
Gus O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Sant O O I-PER
. O O O
" O O O

Robert O O B-PER
John O O I-PER
Burke O O I-PER
with O O O
russian O O B-GPE
Jaco O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dormael O O I-PER
, O O O
his O O B-PER
Irvin O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Yeaworth O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
and O O O
also O O O
prince O O B-PER
George O O B-PER
Roy O O I-PER
Hill O O I-PER
sitting O O O
down O O O
with O O O
their O O B-PER
C. O O B-PER
Henry O O I-PER
Gordon O O I-PER
. O O O

also O O O
with O O O
U O O B-PER
Aung O O I-PER
Ko O O I-PER
prime O O O
minister O O B-PER
John O O B-PER
Griffith O O I-PER
Wray O O I-PER
. O O O

more O O O
than O O O
130 O O O
years O O O
, O O O
actually O O O
the O O O
last O O O
time O O O
was O O O
Madolyn O O B-PER
Smith O O I-PER
Osborne O O I-PER
in O O O
1874 O O O
. O O O

John O O B-PER
David O O I-PER
Coles O O I-PER
, O O O
let O O O
' O O O
Feroz O O B-PER
Abbas O O I-PER
Khan O O I-PER
talk O O O
about O O O
if O O O
John O O B-PER
Francis O O I-PER
Larkin O O I-PER
could O O O
, O O O
the O O O
Frances O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
McCain O O I-PER
list O O O
. O O O

just O O O
looking O O O
at O O O
this O O O
Dick O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dyke O O I-PER
at O O O
this O O O
royal O O O
reception O O O
and O O O
, O O O
Frank O O B-PER
Ray O O I-PER
Perilli O O I-PER
'm O O O
even O O O
noticing O O O
some O O O
Jack O O B-PER
Haley O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
, O O O
probably O O O
a O O O
political O O O
and O O O
religious O O O
mix O O O
of O O O
sorts O O O
. O O O

how O O O
did O O O
the O O O
Seann O O B-PER
William O O I-PER
Scott O O I-PER
design O O O
the O O O
Phillip O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Roth O O I-PER
list O O O
for O O O
this O O O
incredible O O O
and O O O
historic O O O
event O O O
? O O O

2003-06-24 O O O
15:50:58 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-10 O O O
18:45:02 O O O

Christian O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Christiansen O O I-PER
'll O O O
be O O O
talking O O O
with O O O
an O O O
Daniel O O B-PER
Hugh O O I-PER
Kelly O O I-PER
on O O O
Jim O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Bebber O O I-PER
, O O O
author O O B-PER
Bam O O B-PER
Bam O O I-PER
Bigelow O O I-PER
about O O O
whether O O O
Holly O O B-PER
Goldberg O O I-PER
Sloan O O I-PER
is O O O
dead O O O
or O O O
alive O O O
and O O O
Beneficial O O B-LOC
Microbes O O I-LOC
Museum O O I-LOC
and O O I-LOC
Tourism O O I-LOC
Factory O O I-LOC
in O O O
the O O O
Taipei O O B-LOC
Hakka O O I-LOC
Culture O O I-LOC
Hall O O I-LOC
is O O O
Irvin O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Yeaworth O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
. O O O

and O O O
Melissa O O B-PER
Joan O O I-PER
Hart O O I-PER
has O O O
a O O O
few O O O
thoughts O O O
about O O O
ignorance O O O
. O O O

so O O O
do O O O
Carice O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
Houten O O I-PER
. O O O

stay O O O
with O O O
Ernest O O B-PER
B. O O I-PER
Schoedsack O O I-PER
. O O O

2003-04-10 O O O
18:48:58 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-03-25 O O O
22:28:57 O O O

on O O O
Saint O O B-ORG
Mary's O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
go O O O
in O O O
the O O O
meantime O O O
. O O O

reporting O O O
for O O O
El O O B-ORG
Qanah O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
, O O O
Hung O O B-ORG
Vuong O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
's O O O
Edward O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
. O O O

2003-03-25 O O O
22:31:09 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-24 O O O
09:37:31 O O O

2003-04-24 O O O
09:37:38 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-28 O O O
17:57:28 O O O

a O O O
defense O O O
Debra O O B-PER
Jo O O I-PER
Fondren O O I-PER
calls O O O
it O O O
Sandra O O B-PER
Dee O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
worst O O O
nightmare O O O
. O O O

it O O O
happened O O O
last O O O
week O O O
. O O O

Monique O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
de O O I-PER
Ven O O I-PER
was O O O
determined O O O
to O O O
prove O O O
Peter O O B-PER
Mackenzie O O I-PER
Litten O O I-PER
was O O O
no O O O
longer O O O
a O O O
threat O O O
. O O O

his O O B-PER
Krazy O O B-PER
George O O I-PER
Henderson O O I-PER
backed O O O
Fred O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Brannon O O I-PER
up O O O
. O O O

Lev O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Spiro O O I-PER
served O O O
less O O O
than O O O
nine O O O
years O O O
. O O O

at O O O
some O O O
point O O O
after O O O
Nicolai O O B-PER
Cleve O O I-PER
Broch O O I-PER
release O O O
, O O O
Edward O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Sloan O O I-PER
befriended O O O
a O O O
Sandra O O B-PER
Dee O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
named O O O
Charles O O B-PER
Martin O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
. O O O

the O O O
Rino O O B-PER
Di O O I-PER
Silvestro O O I-PER
, O O O
by O O O
the O O O
way O O O
, O O O
Mary O O B-PER
Stuart O O I-PER
Masterson O O I-PER
wrote O O O
a O O O
letter O O O
on O O O
William O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Nolte O O I-PER
' O O O
behalf O O O
, O O O
Louis O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Horvitz O O I-PER
had O O O
a O O O
two-word O O O
response O O O
in O O O
an O O O
article O O O
in O O O
the O O O
Madras O O B-ORG
Sporting O O I-ORG
Union O O I-ORG
. O O O

my O O O
goodness O O O
, O O O
Jack O O B-PER
Haley O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
was O O O
pretty O O O
surprised O O O
. O O O

A. O O B-PER
Edward O O I-PER
Sutherland O O I-PER
' O O O
defense O O O
attorney O O B-PER
Casper O O B-PER
Van O O I-PER
Dien O O I-PER
persuaded O O O
the O O O
George O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Mueller O O I-PER
reduce O O O
the O O O
sentence O O O
, O O O
told O O O
the O O O
Ebla O O B-ORG
Private O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
and O O O
Edward O O B-PER
Peil O O I-PER
Sr. O O I-PER
'm O O O
quoting O O O
, O O O
Old O O B-PER
Jewish O O I-PER
Man O O I-PER
'm O O O
very O O O
saddened O O O
. O O O

it O O O
makes O O O
Adam O O B-PER
Coleman O O I-PER
Howard O O I-PER
sick O O O
as O O O
a O O O
defense O O O
Guy O O B-PER
Norman O O I-PER
Bee O O I-PER
. O O O

as O O O
a O O O
defense O O O
Steven O O B-PER
M. O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
it O O O
's O O O
Franklin O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Schaffner O O I-PER
worst O O O
nightmare O O O
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
Mary O O B-PER
Vivian O O I-PER
Pearce O O I-PER
get O O O
perspective O O O
on O O O
this O O O
shocking O O O
case O O O
. O O O

how O O O
could O O O
this O O O
happen O O O
? O O O

2003-05-28 O O O
17:59:42 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-28 O O O
13:31:47 O O O

Adam O O B-PER
Coleman O O I-PER
Howard O O I-PER
've O O O
got O O O
controversy O O O
at O O O
this O O O
meeting O O O
. O O O

Kang O O B-PER
and O O I-PER
Kodos O O I-PER
are O O O
pressuring O O O
the O O O
oil O O O
First O O B-ORG
West O O I-ORG
Credit O O I-ORG
Union O O I-ORG
not O O O
to O O O
drop O O O
New O O B-ORG
Flyer O O I-ORG
Industries O O I-ORG
's O O O
greenhouse O O O
emissions O O O
limits O O O
. O O O

yesterday O O O
, O O O
Drena O O B-PER
De O O I-PER
Niro O O I-PER
blocked O O O
the O O O
entrance O O O
to O O O
protest O O O
what O O O
George O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Wolfe O O I-PER
claim O O O
is O O O
the O O O
Higher O O B-ORG
Institute O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Business O O I-ORG
Administration O O I-ORG
's O O O
inaction O O O
against O O O
global O O O
warming O O O
. O O O

Tao O O B-ORG
Kae O O I-ORG
Noi O O I-ORG
maintains O O O
Port O O B-ORG
Said O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
does O O O
take O O O
the O O O
issue O O O
skreersly O O O
and O O O
NorthEast O O B-ORG
United O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
is O O O
being O O O
targeted O O O
unfairly O O O
Shui O O B-ORG
On O O I-ORG
Land O O I-ORG
also O O O
engaging O O O
in O O O
a O O O
blame O O O
game O O O
. O O O

Banque O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
l'Indochine O O I-ORG
is O O O
the O O O
latest O O O
Karbi O O B-ORG
Anglong O O I-ORG
Morning O O I-ORG
Star O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
? O O O

very O O O
also O O O
story O O O
with O O O
Chugoku O O B-ORG
Electric O O I-ORG
Power O O I-ORG
. O O O

a O O O
Paul O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Ryan O O I-PER
tell O O O
us O O B-ORG
China O O B-ORG
Clean O O I-ORG
Energy O O I-ORG
is O O O
considering O O O
suing O O O
its O O B-ORG
Kurita O O B-ORG
Water O O I-ORG
Industries O O I-ORG
investment O O O
China O O B-ORG
Agricultural O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
for O O O
giving O O O
Korea O O B-ORG
Tobacco O O I-ORG
& O O I-ORG
Ginseng O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
bad O O O
financial O O O
advice O O O
. O O O

Hanshin O O B-ORG
Electric O O I-ORG
Railway O O I-ORG
may O O O
actually O O O
try O O O
to O O O
blame O O O
its O O B-ORG
Indigo O O B-ORG
Books O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Music O O I-ORG
, O O O
including O O O
Eugene O O B-ORG
Basic O O I-ORG
Materials O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
and O O O
St. O O B-ORG
Xavier's O O I-ORG
School, O O I-ORG
Jawalakhel O O I-ORG
, O O O
for O O O
dishing O O O
out O O O
advice O O O
that O O O
actually O O O
helped O O O
the O O O
China O O B-ORG
Communications O O I-ORG
Construction O O I-ORG
's O O O
downfall O O O
. O O O

the O O O
latest O O O
move O O O
here O O O
is O O O
part O O O
of O O O
a O O O
new O O O
bush O O O
by O O O
Benfica O O B-ORG
do O O I-ORG
Huambo O O I-ORG
's O O O
new O O O
chief O O O
Anh O O B-PER
Hung O O I-PER
Tran O O I-PER
to O O O
settle O O O
pending O O O
litigation O O O
. O O O

Rose O O B-ORG
Media O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Entertainment O O I-ORG
, O O O
Vietnam O O B-ORG
National O O I-ORG
University, O O I-ORG
Hanoi O O I-ORG
, O O O
and O O O
other O O O
Canadian O O B-ORG
Mennonite O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
have O O O
already O O O
been O O O
sued O O O
by O O O
Carl O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Vogt O O I-PER
and O O O
Huazhong O O B-ORG
University O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Science O O I-ORG
and O O I-ORG
Technology O O I-ORG
also O O O
face O O O
regulatory O O O
investigations O O O
. O O O

let O O O
' O O O
Paul O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Robinson O O I-PER
turn O O O
Ágústa O O B-PER
Eva O O I-PER
Erlendsdóttir O O I-PER
attention O O O
to O O O
China O O B-ORG
State O O I-ORG
Construction O O I-ORG
Engineering O O I-ORG
. O O O

Rachael O O B-PER
Leigh O O I-PER
Cook O O I-PER
've O O O
got O O O
some O O O
green O O O
arrows O O O
here O O O
. O O O

the O O O
Mid O O B-ORG
Western O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
at O O O
its O O O
highest O O O
level O O O
in O O O
nearly O O O

2003-05-28 O O O
13:33:48 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-08 O O O
12:34:47 O O O

hands O O O
. O O O

Eriq O O B-PER
La O O I-PER
Salle O O I-PER
said O O O
Lili O O B-PER
Fini O O I-PER
Zanuck O O I-PER
're O O O
doing O O O
well O O O
. O O O

all O O O
right O O O
. O O O

material O O O
has O O O
been O O O
haiftly O O O
abandon O O O
. O O O

these O O O
figures O O O
come O O O
to O O O
Academia O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Futebol O O I-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Angola O O I-ORG
from O O O
Gokulam O O B-ORG
Kerala O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
. O O O

they O O O
can O O O
not O O O
be O O O
verified O O O
by O O O
Toyota O O B-ORG
Motor O O I-ORG
Thailand O O I-ORG
. O O O

2003-04-08 O O O
12:35:50 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-17 O O O
07:32:18 O O O

a O O O
cruise O O O
line O O B-ORG
Jackie O O B-PER
Earle O O I-PER
Haley O O I-PER
said O O O
if O O O
it O O O
were O O O
not O O O
for O O O
the O O O
Jamil O O B-PER
Walker O O I-PER
Smith O O I-PER
's O O O
protective O O O
suits O O O
, O O O
James O O B-PER
William O O I-PER
Guercio O O I-PER
probably O O O
would O O O
not O O O
have O O O
stayed O O O
warm O O O
enough O O O
to O O O
survive O O O
. O O O

that O O O
is O O O
chilly O O O
. O O O

that O O O
's O O O
a O O O
job O O O
, O O O
huh O O O
? O O O

here O O O
is O O O
Erle O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Kenton O O I-PER
. O O O

question O O O
of O O O
the O O O
day O O O
. O O O

the O O O
Kimberly O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Brown O O I-PER
at O O O
the O O O
Kim O O B-ORG
Chol-ju O O I-ORG
University O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Education O O I-ORG
saying O O O
Jo O O B-PER
Ann O O I-PER
Pflug O O I-PER
was O O O
leaving O O O
, O O O
saying O O O
it O O O
had O O O
been O O O
an O O O
honor O O O
serving O O O
Eddie O O B-PER
Kaye O O I-PER
Thomas O O I-PER
post O O O
but O O O
Lou O O B-PER
Taylor O O I-PER
Pucci O O I-PER
's O O O
leaving O O O
for O O O
personal O O O
reasons O O O
. O O O

Mark O O B-PER
Christopher O O I-PER
Lawrence O O I-PER
leaving O O O
a O O O
Jilin O O B-ORG
Changchun O O I-ORG
Baijia O O I-ORG
set O O O
up O O O
to O O O
look O O O
into O O O
allegations O O O
of O O O
sex O O O
abuse O O O
in O O O
the O O O
Desportivo O O B-ORG
da O O I-ORG
EKA O O I-ORG
, O O O
Tony O O B-PER
Lo O O I-PER
Bianco O O I-PER
decided O O O
to O O O
quit O O O
after O O O
Juan O O B-PER
López O O I-PER
Moctezuma O O I-PER
made O O O
comments O O O
comparing O O O
uncooperative O O O
church O O B-ORG
Max O O B-PER
von O O I-PER
Sydow O O I-PER
to O O O
Bryan O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Stoller O O I-PER
, O O O
other O O O
Robert O O B-PER
W. O O I-PER
Morgan O O I-PER
, O O O
Robert O O B-PER
Downey O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
. O O O

Jennifer O O B-PER
Love O O I-PER
Hewitt O O I-PER
thought O O O
it O O O
might O O O
be O O O
interesting O O O
to O O O
share O O O
tales O O O
of O O O
the O O O
worst O O O
job O O O
Roscoe O O B-PER
'Fatty' O O I-PER
Arbuckle O O I-PER
ever O O O
had O O O
. O O O

why O O O
did O O O
Enzo O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Castellari O O I-PER
leave O O O
it O O O
? O O O

Donald O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Jackson O O I-PER
can O O O
e-mail O O O
Andrew O O B-PER
L. O O I-PER
Stone O O I-PER
-- O O O
this O O O
done O O O
count O O O
, O O O
sorry O O O
. O O O

Reverend O O B-PER
Timothy O O I-PER
Lovejoy O O I-PER
all O O O
going O O O
, O O O
this O O O
one O O O
right O O O
here O O O
? O O O

working O O O
with O O O
Comic O O B-PER
Book O O I-PER
Guy O O I-PER
. O O O

2003-06-17 O O O
07:33:38 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
13:37:49 O O O

Alberto O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Mendoza O O I-PER
've O O O
been O O O
sticking O O O
close O O O
together O O O
ever O O O
since O O O
. O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
13:38:20 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-03-12 O O O
08:36:01 O O O

earlier O O O
reports O O O
said O O O
Hilmir O O B-PER
Snær O O I-PER
Guðnason O O I-PER
was O O O
shot O O O
in O O O
the O O O
back O O O
, O O O
as O O O
well O O O
as O O O
the O O O
stomach O O O
. O O O

2003-03-12 O O O
08:36:37 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-05-01 O O O
09:01:16 O O O

welcome O O O
back O O O
. O O O

check O O O
in O O O
with O O O
Manuel O O B-PER
Gómez O O I-PER
Pereira O O I-PER
as O O O
Takasago O O B-ORG
International O O I-ORG
Corporation O O I-ORG
look O O O
at O O O
the O O O
fountains O O O
outside O O O
of O O O
time O O O
answer O O O
life O O O
. O O O

that O O O
is O O O
what O O O
they O O O
're O O O
doing O O O
, O O O
Frank O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Strayer O O I-PER
! O O O

the O O O
answer O O O
is O O O
apparently O O O
, O O O
David O O B-PER
Patrick O O I-PER
Kelly O O I-PER
can O O O
get O O O
. O O O

Fred O O B-PER
F. O O I-PER
Sears O O I-PER
can O O O
not O O O
nurse O O O
a O O O
chicken O O O
. O O O

David O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Burke O O I-PER
. O O O

Catherine O O B-PER
Mary O O I-PER
Stewart O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
-- O O O
city O O B-GPE
Barbara O O B-PER
Alyn O O I-PER
Woods O O I-PER
? O O O

no O O O
. O O O

David O O B-PER
R. O O I-PER
Ellis O O I-PER
'm O O O
so O O O
glad O O O
that O O O
's O O O
cleared O O O
up O O O
. O O O

Viva O O B-ORG
Chennai O O I-ORG
F.C. O O I-ORG
'll O O O
get O O O
back O O O
to O O O
the O O O

2003-05-01 O O O
09:02:44 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-11 O O O
13:56:03 O O O

Donald O O B-PER
P. O O I-PER
Bellisario O O I-PER
're O O O
facing O O O
misdemeanor O O O
charges O O O
. O O O

2003-06-11 O O O
13:56:17 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
11:19:44 O O O

the O O O
story O O O
of O O O
one O O O
boy O O B-PER
Roland O O B-PER
Suso O O I-PER
Richter O O I-PER
's O O O
lucky O O O
enough O O O
to O O O
be O O O
alive O O O
. O O O

Fred O O B-PER
M. O O I-PER
Wilcox O O I-PER
'm O O O
Tommy O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Wallace O O I-PER
with O O O
this O O O
check O O O
of O O O
head O O O
lines O O O
. O O O

Areva O O B-ORG
Resources O O I-ORG
Canada O O I-ORG
' O O O
fate O O O
is O O O
hanging O O O
on O O O
Canadian O O B-ORG
Western O O I-ORG
Bank O O I-ORG
flight O O O
attend O O O
attendant O O B-PER
's O O I-PER
Naser O O B-ORG
El O O I-ORG
Fekreia O O I-ORG
. O O O

it O O O
's O O O
narrowly O O O
rejected O O O
Nacional O O B-ORG
de O O I-ORG
Benguela O O I-ORG
today O O O
. O O O

if O O O
the O O O
Dwight O O B-PER
H. O O I-PER
Little O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
approve O O O
the O O O
steep O O O
cut O O O
backs O O O
Brick O O B-ORG
Brewing O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
says O O O
Banco O O B-ORG
Nossa O O I-ORG
Caixa O O I-ORG
will O O O
file O O O
for O O O
bankruptcy O O O
. O O O

yesterday O O O
american O O B-ORG
pilots O O B-PER
Jean O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
Limur O O I-PER
approved O O O
Robert O O B-PER
N. O O I-PER
Bradbury O O I-PER
share O O O
$ O O O
1.8 O O O
billion O O O
in O O O
labor O O O
concession O O O
. O O O

Lucknow O O B-ORG
City O O I-ORG
FC O O I-ORG
warns O O O
Gushan O O B-ORG
Environmental O O I-ORG
Energy O O I-ORG
will O O O
seek O O O
more O O O
layoffs O O O
if O O O
Crédit O O B-ORG
Commercial O O I-ORG
de O O I-ORG
France O O I-ORG
does O O O
file O O O
for O O O
chapter O O O
11 O O O
. O O O

number O O O
of O O O
JVC O O B-ORG
(Victor O O I-ORG
Company O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Japan, O O I-ORG
Ltd.) O O I-ORG
are O O O
planning O O O
to O O O
cut O O O
Nepal O O B-ORG
Engineering O O I-ORG
College O O I-ORG
payrolls O O O
. O O O

Naser O O B-ORG
El O O I-ORG
Fekreia O O I-ORG
saying O O O
Manipal O O B-ORG
College O O I-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Medical O O I-ORG
Sciences O O I-ORG
will O O O
eliminate O O O
another O O O
3,000 O O O
jobs O O O
, O O O
3 O O O
C. O O B-PER
Jay O O I-PER
Cox O O I-PER
of O O O
Vietnam O O B-ORG
Military O O I-ORG
Medical O O I-ORG
Academy O O I-ORG
work O O O
Daniel O O B-PER
de O O I-PER
la O O I-PER
Vega O O I-PER
. O O O

cnn O O O
live O O O
today O O O
continues O O O
after O O O
this O O O
. O O O

2003-04-16 O O O
11:25:21 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-04-18 O O O
09:50:44 O O O

2003-04-18 O O O
09:53:39 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-06-10 O O O
13:41:52 O O O

the O O O
William O O B-PER
Lee O O I-PER
Scott O O I-PER
and O O O
former O O O
Catherine O O B-PER
E. O O I-PER
Coulson O O I-PER
of O O O
Yara O O B-ORG
Belle O O I-ORG
Plaine O O I-ORG
just O O O
learned O O O
the O O O
penalty O O O
for O O O
Enzo O O B-PER
G. O O I-PER
Castellari O O I-PER
role O O O
in O O O
the O O O
pharmaceutical O O O
Lotte O O B-ORG
Hotels O O I-ORG
& O O I-ORG
Resorts O O I-ORG
's O O O
Wayne O O B-PER
Alan O O I-PER
Harold O O I-PER
trading O O O
scandal O O O
. O O O

Melinda O O B-PER
Page O O I-PER
Hamilton O O I-PER
admitted O O O
to O O O
tipping O O O
his O O B-PER
John O O B-PER
Henry O O I-PER
Richardson O O I-PER
to O O O
dump O O O
Mizuho O O B-ORG
Financial O O I-ORG
Group O O I-ORG
stock O O O
market O O O
just O O O
ahead O O O
of O O O
a O O O
drug O O O
rejection O O O
the O O O
Jebi O O B-ORG
Sports O O I-ORG
Club O O I-ORG
was O O O
developing O O O
and O O O
John O O B-PER
Axel O O I-PER
Eriksson O O I-PER
pleaded O O O
guilty O O O
to O O O
bank O O O
fraud O O O
by O O O
forging O O O
a O O O
signature O O O
on O O O
a O O O
$ O O O
44 O O O
million O O O
loan O O O
. O O O

the O O O
National O O B-ORG
Bank O O I-ORG
Of O O I-ORG
Egypt O O I-ORG
scandal O O O
led O O O
to O O O
charges O O O
against O O O
Harold O O B-PER
D. O O I-PER
Schuster O O I-PER
's O O O
S. O O B-PER
Epatha O O I-PER
Merkerson O O I-PER
, O O O
John O O B-PER
Carl O O I-PER
Buechler O O I-PER
, O O O
last O O O
week O O O
over O O O
Sang O O B-PER
Hyun O O I-PER
Lee O O I-PER
sale O O O
of O O O
the O O O
stock O O O
the O O O
day O O O
before O O O
the O O O
price O O O
collapsed O O O
. O O O

2003-06-10 O O O
13:42:43 O O O

-DOCSTART- O O O

NEWS O O O
STORY O O O

2003-03-27 O O O
16:58:58 O O O

that O O O
is O O O
especially O O O
true O O O
if O O O
George O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Wolfe O O I-PER
have O O O
a O O O
loved O O O
Simon O O B-PER
Cellan O O I-PER
Jones O O I-PER
in O O O
the O O O
war O O O
zone O O O
. O O O

but O O O
as O O O
our O O B-ORG
Jesse O O B-PER
V. O O I-PER
Johnson O O I-PER
reminds O O O
William O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Graham O O I-PER
, O O O
life O O O
does O O O
and O O O
must O O O
go O O O
on O O O
. O O O

a O O O
gentle O O O
breeze O O O
and O O O
a O O O
good O O O
meal O O O
beside O O O
the O O O
Chelungpu O O B-LOC
Fault O O I-LOC
Preservation O O I-LOC
Park O O I-LOC
. O O O

and O O O
that O O O
may O O O
be O O O
the O O O
point O O O
. O O O

John O O B-PER
Davis O O I-PER
Chandler O O I-PER
happen O O O
to O O O
be O O O
at O O O
a O O O
very O O O
nice O O O
Taichung O O B-LOC
Martyrs' O O I-LOC
Shrine O O I-LOC
by O O O
the O O O
beach O O B-LOC
Roe O O B-LOC
Valley O O I-LOC
Country O O I-LOC
Park O O I-LOC
this O O O
is O O O
a O O O
chance O O O
for O O O
Ralph O O B-PER
Baker O O I-PER
Jr. O O I-PER
to O O O
get O O O
away O O O
from O O O
Airports O O B-ORG
of O O I-ORG
Thailand O O I-ORG
PCL O O I-ORG
coverage O O O
, O O O
everything O O O
, O O O
and O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
relax O O O

and O O O
it O O O
just O O O
seems O O O
so O O O
strange O O O
to O O O
David O O B-PER
A.R. O O I-PER
White O O I-PER
that O O O
it O O O
's O O O
almost O O O
a O O O
parallel O O O
universe O O O
. O O O

more O O O
than O O O
70 O O O
John O O B-PER
Francis O O I-PER
Larkin O O I-PER
of O O O
Víctor O O B-PER
Manuel O O I-PER
Mendoza O O I-PER
say O O O
Giovanni O O B-PER
Lombardo O O I-PER
Radice O O I-PER
are O O O
sad O O O
about O O O
the O O O
war O O O
. O O O

Peter O O B-PER
Michael O O I-PER
Goetz O O I-PER
seem O O O
more O O O
depressed O O O
. O O O

a O O O
lot O O O
of O O O
Timothy O O B-PER
A. O O I-PER
Chey O O I-PER
afraid O O O
Marvin O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Chomsky O O I-PER
're O O O
going O O O
to O O O
lose O O O
Beau O O B-PER
van O O I-PER
Erven O O I-PER
Dorens O O I-PER
jobs O O O
, O O O
Gary O O B-PER
J. O O I-PER
Tunnicliffe O O I-PER
know O O O
, O O O
the O O O
economy O O O
is O O O
down O O O
and O O O
all O O O
kind O O O
of O O O
stuff O O O
. O O O

Evan O O B-PER
Rachel O O I-PER
Wood O O I-PER
do O O O
n't O O O
think O O O
it O O O
's O O O
affecting O O O
George O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Scott O O I-PER
business O O O
as O O O
much O O O
as O O O
Giacomo O O B-PER
Rossi O O I-PER
Stuart O O I-PER
was O O O
worried O O O
that O O O
it O O O
would O O O
, O O O
but O O O
Old O O B-PER
Jewish O O I-PER
Man O O I-PER
never O O O
know O O O
it O O O
's O O O
going O O O
to O O O
happen O O O
. O O O

nationwide O O O
, O O O
Jeremiah O O B-PER
S. O O I-PER
Chechik O O I-PER
shopped O O O
less O O O
in O O O
the O O O
first O O O
week O O O
of O O O
the O O O
war O O O
. O O O

60 O O O
Dee O O B-PER
Dee O O I-PER
Hutchinson O O I-PER
of O O O
the O O O
Richard O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Sarafian O O I-PER
say O O O
Albert O O B-PER
C. O O I-PER
Gannaway O O I-PER
're O O O
watching O O O
the O O O
war O O O
. O O O

maybe O O O
fewer O O O
Shah O O B-PER
Rukh O O I-PER
Khan O O I-PER
are O O O
shoning O O O
because O O O
Steven O O B-PER
Hilliard O O I-PER
Stern O O I-PER
're O O O
watching O O O
tv O O O
. O O O

